What's up?!
Today's stream is a little special.
Because it is exactly two years, four years, since I did my first stream.
Everything I just said was a lie, I'm sorry.
It's not even true.
But there is something special about today.
4 Colossus!
Guys, I'm going to attempt to play Minecraft with my foot.
You think I'm kidding?
I'm not.
I'm not lying.
Because I determined last time that I played Minecraft, you know what?
The game was a little too easy.
And you may say, well, you died a bunch and all that.
But you know what?
That was part of the script.
I'm actually so good at the game, today I'm not going to die a single time.
And I will be playing with my foot.
One hand on keyboard, the other hand on a trackball.
I'm not fucking with you.
No foot cam.
We're not doing foot cam.
Oh man!
Also, sorry about the audio levels here.
Let me just...
Turn that down a bit.
Don't mind.
It's so hard to control the mouse with my foot.
Holy shit.
Wow.
I hope you're all having a great day.
It's a bit of an early stream because I just couldn't wait.
I was going to play Minecraft in like two hours.
But I was like, I really want to play now!
So I'm just going to do that.
You know?
Be happy.
Do the things you love at the times you love them.
And I love them now.
Let me consider doing a transition here.
Let me see if I can do this with my foot.
Oh my god, it's so hard.
With my foot.
Okay!
There it is.
How are y'all doing, huh?
I'm so behind on this series and Create confuses me so bad.
That makes two of us.
Create is confusing.
It's not easy.
It's very hard to figure out.
But it's fun.
That's the most important thing.
While things may be slow.
I'm having a blast with it.
Just slowly figuring it out.
It's great.
It's actually really lovely.
You know?
I still have a bunch of stuff that I know I haven't done yet.
And Create.
And it's nice.
Knowing that.
That I have that to look forward to, you know?
I know I can make airplanes.
Obviously trains are on my mind a lot lately.
So we're going to be doing that.
At least try to.
Maybe today is the day we do trains.
In any case, today will be the day of progress.
As the title of the stream is saying.
I have a feeling.
It's in my tummy.
And I can feel it.
It's in the top left part of my tummy.
It actually kind of hurts.
But it's there.
And I'm going to be playing with my foot.
Wish me luck with that.
Not bad!
I managed to click.
Okay, hold on.
I need to...
Oh yeah.
Oh my god.
It's so weird.
That's so weird.
How am I ever going to...
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Wait, I need to...
Maybe increase...
Nice sensitivity!
Let's put it at like...
Three.
Oh my god.
It's so hard to hit correctly.
Wee!
Nice.
Alright.
Today's a special day.
Because...
We are finally at our peak.
Check this out.
Smite 4.
Fire Aspect 2.
Efficiency 4.
Unbreaking 3.
Efficiency 5!
Although with Silk Touch.
So I'm not a big fan of Silk Touch, but that's okay.
And we also have Armor.
With Protection 4 on their legs.
That's actually amazing.
We have an insane bow!
With Power 5 and everything.
Oh my god.
This is gonna be so weird.
Ah!
Jesus Christ!
That's hard.
No, okay.
Listen.
I am actually playing with my foot, but it's because my hand is hurting.
There's something on my wrist today.
I don't know what it is, but it's kind of hurting.
I gotta go to the doctor with that.
So I'm playing with my foot!
Uh, so...
If I die today...
It is because of that.
It is not because I'm bad at the game.
Just so you know.
Alright.
What's up, Frank?
Or whatever your name is.
I actually forgot the names of these animals.
That's unfortunate.
But you know what?
They are, uh...
They have different names.
For the different times of the year.
That's what we're gonna say.
Okay.
We made it to the end last time, and we managed to kill the dragon.
After many trials and tribulations.
It was quite an ordeal.
Today, though...
Things will change.
Because now that we have all this, I'm gonna go collect all kinds of exotic materials.
We're gonna find Netherite today.
We're gonna go back to the end.
Because I wanna find, uh...
One of those cities.
And I wanna rob them of all their belongings, you know?
Now that I have all this on me.
It's gonna be great.
Uh...
What is even in here?
Wait, how do I...
Wait, how do I scroll?
Oh, okay.
That's how you do it.
Okay, there's nothing in there.
Wait, uh...
B...
Oh, that's much better.
Okay, so we have a wrench...
Headcrank.
Okay, okay.
Oh my god.
There we go.
Let's take this and put it...
There.
Oh no!
Wait.
I need to see what else I can make.
No, should I be...
Hold on.
Uh, didn't I get a...
Last time I brought home new stuff, didn't I?
So we should've unlocked something new.
Maybe I'll try this gantry shaft thing.
Today.
The gantry carriage.
Block of raw sink.
Stock ticker.
Da
da da da da.
John is shining, where there's good.
I loooove life!
It's beautiful...
Ah, it's a feeling.
Okay.
Anyway.
Let's- Let's go back to the end.
I'm gonna go back!
Especially now that we're level 2.
We have nothing to lose.
Everything is fine.
Throw that away.
Dude, it's impossible to play like this.
I'm not even kidding.
Whoops!
Oh my god.
Oh, I thought I broke it.
Nice.
Uh, wait.
B.
Hoo hoo hoo.
Wait, how do I... Oh yeah, this way.
Do I have everything I need?
I need to get a boat.
I don't even know, man.
I'm just... You know what?
Okay, listen.
I'm just existing right now, okay?
Allow me to just exist in Minecraft.
Give me this, okay?
Uh, let's bring a water bucket.
Wait, wait, wait, whoa.
Okay, nevermind.
Should I bring a fish?
Yo!
Actually, we're gonna go fishing.
We're gonna bring a boat.
And a bed.
Well...
Uh, we also have some bows here, but they're not important.
Ooh, this one now is enchanted.
Wait, less burning time!
I never noticed this!
It's because it's a diving tank!
It makes so much sense!
Oh my god.
Maybe I should use that in the nether.
You know?
Not to be burning.
Flint and steel.
I think I'm ready, honestly.
We got arrows.
This one does not have infinity.
So we should actually bring more.
This is not enough.
No way, Jose.
Oh yeah, right.
That's how you right click.
Um...
Whee!
So much fun.
Moving the cursor.
You know what I mean?
It's one of those things.
Okay, we're gonna make the...
Specialized arrows.
Boop!
Fourteen.
Was that a waste?
Maybe it's a waste.
I don't know.
Boop!
No!
Wait, how do I...
There we go.
Holy crap!
Wow!
Hi Raul!
I may close the door behind me.
Look at these train tracks.
Imagine for a moment a train on top of those tracks.
I'm seeing it clear right now.
Cheers.
It may happen today.
It could happen to you!
Don't forget it.
Oh, wait, we don't have enough food.
Ah, but we have fire aspectus.
The fire conspectus shall make it all good.
We're gonna find a bunch of cows and murder them.
God, I'm actually so...
Dude, I'm surprisingly okay with my foot.
In this game.
I could walk over this, but I'm not gonna.
I think I'll take the scenic route.
Oh my god, it's actually so imprecise.
Look, if I'm trying to aim, it's like...
I can do circles pretty well.
Circles are good.
I'm just...
Right now, I'm just using my pinky on my foot.
That's weird, man.
That's weird!
That you can do that?
Okay, you know what?
I'm getting lost.
I need to cross land.
What is that sound I'm hearing?
I think someone is vacuuming in the other room.
So weird.
Can we get some music in there?
Now.
Oh, imagine though.
Imagine.
AHHHHH!
Bastard!
Oops.
Fucking timing.
Jesus Christ.
La la la, I'm lying.
Every day, I like to lie.
It's the best.
We're gonna go kill some animals with this fire aspect.
Also, that was a lie just now.
I don't lie every day.
Only every other day.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehe.
Oh my god.
Guys, I'm in such a fricking good mood today man.
It's hard to explain.
No, it's not.
I'm in a good mood, boom.
There, explain it.
I just... you know, it's one of those days...
Where no matter what's happening, it's just good times, you know?
Someone's breaking in, stealing your wallet, you know, tying your feet.
Doesn't matter.
Good times.
It's a good day.
The cheese falls out of the fridge, you know, lands on the floor, and you know you gotta throw it out.
It's okay.
It's a good day.
I don't know why I picked that up.
Throw it away.
Need to destroy that.
I wanna hear the creative music, man.
It doesn't happen often, enough for me.
Wait, where am I going?
Oh yeah, I'm going to the stronghold.
And I know where it is, because there's like 8 million boats over there.
I remember that island.
It's such a weird feeling.
But I guess it's good for my foot anyway.
You know, like getting...
You know what I should've gone?
I should've gotten one of those, um...
Massage balls inserted into the trackball for my foot.
You know, so that I can play the game and massage my feet at the same time.
Imagine that for a moment.
And then I want you to imagine what it would've been like if you were born blind.
Can you do that for me?
Wait, where are these ships?
Oops.
Oh, it's over here.
I keep getting confused.
Cheers guys.
Happy Wednesday, I believe.
Or Thursday.
Let me see.
What day is it today?
It is Wednesday!
Incredible.
For no reason at all, I'm happy.
Earlier is better than later.
Am I right or what?
Whoops.
Ah, there we go.
There it is.
We found it.
We're not gonna die a single time.
In the rest of this world.
Not just today, but like forever.
In fact, I'll never die in Minecraft again.
And you know what?
I believe it.
You may think, oh, you die all the time.
I feel it in my bones that I'm right about this.
You know?
Oh, there it is.
Uh, this should be, yeah, safe to fall down.
Great.
Let's get some air.
And...
Go!
Speeding...
Oh no.
Huh?!
Okay, wait.
I fucked it up.
It's so weird playing...
I like...
You don't understand how hard it is to play like this.
There we go.
Maximum speed.
That's the guy from Crysis, sis.
Maximum power.
Yeah, come on.
There we go.
Honey, I'm home!
Uh, wait.
Why?
Did I not...
Oh!
Oh my god!
Bro...
Just get the fuck out of me.
I'm gonna kill you.
You're gonna die.
And come down to me.
Let's have some...
Wait, you can't even pass.
Oh!
Wait a minute!
I got you now!
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Hey, wait a second!
Maybe I should farm some pearls.
If I'm gonna go, you know, jumping between islands, we definitely need the pearl-o's.
Don't we?
Let's farm some pearls.
There.
Beautiful.
Look at me aiming precisely with my appendages.
Or just the- just the one appendage, actually.
Oh my god, it's so loud in my ear!
Ahhhh!
Jesus!
Hold on, I gotta take off my headphone.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, you have to suffer.
I'm not suffering, you're suffering.
I'm dying!
I'm gonna block with my foot.
I literally, physically cannot hit the block button while I'm doing this.
I need the, uh, I need to be able to hit multiple at a time.
Oh!
Wait, they're pushing me!
Oh god!
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
Oh nice!
More pearls!
Come on, I'm not done with you.
We're almost done here!
Well, almost.
Oh, come on!
Oh god.
Oh shit, I'm- How are they hitting me?
It's like they're bugging through the wall and hitting me.
They're no clipping.
Okay, I put on my headphones again.
Whew, that was inventful.
How many did I get?
Eight!
Ooh, nice.
We can do that again.
I'm not done.
Oh, we have a better one right here!
Let's use this.
Okay, now, aim.
God, it is so imprecise.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
Murder!
Love me some murdering.
This is semi-genocide.
But it's for a good cause.
You know how it is.
The greater good.
Oh, wait, how are they hitting me?
Whoa!
I'm dying, I'm dying, I'm dead.
Dude, I cannot aim.
I may have to go over to my hand again.
Like, I can't play like this.
It feels like I'm stepping on them.
Whoops.
Jesus Christ.
Give me that.
Getting a decent amount of experience, too.
Not amazing, but, you know, some.
Also, how on earth are...
Oh!
They died out here, some of them, because they were burning!
That explains a lot!
Right.
Actually, the burning is probably helping a lot here with the DPS.
I'm gonna take one of these.
Oh, shit.
We're fine.
We're gonna block this now, because this was a problem area.
Like that.
This should be okay now.
Let's do one last round of killing, and then we're gonna embark on an expedition.
Come on, look at their faces!
And now, stand still.
Don't touch the keyboard.
Just move your feet.
Clap your hands.
A brand new dance.
Nice.
I think they're so wild, because they are burning, you know?
They're jumping all over the place, they're confused.
They don't know what's happening.
They were chilling in their home dimension, and all of a sudden, this guy comes in and just starts slapping ass, you know?
Come on.
Oh, that was a nice aim!
You saw that?
Remember this is it!
Jesus.
I thought we were done!
Are we not done?
We're not done.
I just wanna kill one more!
Where are you?
There we go!
We're done.
Okay.
Now, I see it already over here.
We're gonna go up through that portal.
Unless there's more.
Ooh!
24 pearls.
Guys.
With my feet.
Oh, is this maybe too risky, actually?
Let's not do this.
Oh, and we're digging so fast now, because we have enchants.
Let's just do this.
Also, wait a second.
If I go through the portal now.
Like the portal in the center, I mean.
I should appear in my home, right?
And not at spawn.
Because I slept there last.
At least I hope I did.
Which means I can't sleep in this bed I have here.
Well, I can, but not in here, you know?
We're gonna make a nice staircase to this thing, because we're probably gonna go in there a lot.
And stone.
Okay.
Anything... new?
No.
Okay.
Okay, so how am I gonna do this in a good way?
I could just go straight up.
Man, what is the best way to make a staircase?
Without knowing the range.
I guess I can just start over here, and then...
If I'm too...
Early, I just make it horizontal.
But even then, I can't...
Wait, I can't actually do that.
I mean, I can go a little bit of the way.
Dude, I hate this!
I'm just gonna...
Make a pillar.
Right here.
And now, the way to get down...
I guess you can...
Yeah, hold on a minute, actually.
Oh!
That's how you do it, but it's gonna progressively cost more and more blocks, you know?
It's not ideal.
Yeah, and at some point you can't even reach that, so that's gonna be annoying.
I guess we can just jump down now.
Ow.
Let's go up.
Like that.
Oh my god!
I just slipped my foot on the controls.
Dude, I think I found the most efficient way to do this.
Obviously, I did it slow, but you know what?
You can do it faster.
You know what I mean.
Beautiful.
And now we have a nice staircase.
Okay, you know what, actually?
I am gonna disregard the foot.
WAH!
Dude, I was pushing the fucking trackball away with my foot!
And I accidentally clicked!
Imagine if I clicked in empty space, I would have died!
I'm so lucky!
I'm so lucky that I actually went through the hole.
Holy shit!
Wow!
Hold on, get this fucking thing out of the way.
Okay, back to mouse.
I can't be in here with a foot, man.
Holy crap!
Wait, oh my mouse is so slow now!
Why is that?
Wait a minute, something's wrong.
I need to fix something.
Why the hell is my mouse so slow?
Let
me see.
Oh, that's better.
I forgot I had special settings for the foot controller.
Wait, I don't have any food!
I can't believe I did this!
Oh my god, look at that!
Oh wait, there's food on the trees.
We can eat the trees.
We're gonna eat the dogs and the cats.
We're gonna eat the pets.
And the roots.
And everything else.
We're gonna eat everyone.
Yeah, let's just make a nice and safe bridge here.
We're not taking any chances at all.
It's so weird playing with a mouse again.
And then...
I'm gonna make a little extra here because I don't trust like that, you know?
Kinda running out of blocks.
Let's do this.
I'm gonna shave off a little bit of the edge here.
It's been so long since I was in here.
In this place.
Also, weren't there achievements here?
This one.
Okay.
Oh wait a minute.
Collect dragon's breath in a glass bottle.
I never tried this!
Why didn't I do this before I killed the dragon?
Oh no!
We're gonna have to respawn the dragon, man.
But I don't remember what it was.
How to do it.
And the worst part is, I was told.
It was something about, uh, torches.
I remember that.
Torches in the center.
It's just music!
Nothing to be afraid of!
The fuck?
That makes no sense.
Dude, I kinda miss my foot right now.
Yeah, let's just go this way.
Wait.
There's a faster way to do this.
Oh!
Look at this!
Peak efficiency achieved!
Except we're not quite aligned.
I'm not even moving my hand or anything.
I'm just going.
Oh shit.
It's not pretty anymore, but that's okay.
I like the tracks in here.
They're nice.
Okay, now we go straight.
Straight engaged!
Oh.
Safety blocks.
There we go.
Ooh!
Wait!
Oh, it's something about blasting, I guess.
It's gotta be blasting related.
Let me see here.
What's new?
Show me the wobble.
Pop the chorus fruit.
Wait, it's actually blasting!
Wait, what?
What?
Huh!
Weird.
I thought you had to cook that.
But okay.
Uh, eating this will teleport me.
So I'm not gonna eat it yet.
Also, what I'm gonna do is...
Before I forget...
We're gonna make a sort of...
Little indicator.
So we don't forget where we came from.
Actually very important.
Make a bridge.
Uh, no.
Just a single file.
The question is...
Are we gonna find something good in here?
Unfortunately, it doesn't look like there's one of those floating ships.
So...
Elytra is gonna have to be...
Uh...
Down the road.
Literally.
I have 44 of these now.
I forgot the mechanics exactly with these.
Like, sometimes they bounce off the arrows.
And I don't know why.
Probably just when they're closed, right?
What?!
I touched you?!
Minotachi!
Come here.
Uh, oh!
Hello, sir.
Where are you?
How did you hit me?!
I have my shield up, man.
By the way, this is no joke right now.
I don't have good food.
This is...
Like, scary and dangerous.
I can't take too much damage.
Cause eating this will put me in danger.
Cause I'll teleport out into the open.
Did he die from my fire?
I think...
Yeah, he died.
Great.
Okay.
Now, I just got something, didn't I?
Did I unlock something?
I mean, other than the...
chest, I guess.
Okay.
What about these things?
Let's just grab a bit of everything.
Endstone bricks.
And these are...
Purpur.
Oh!
Dude, for a second I thought I was falling into the abyss.
Now you know what my fears are.
In this moment.
Oh, I see you.
Is this thing gonna come down here or what?
Hello?
Just utilize the natural staircase.
Oh shit.
Wait, what the...
I see you up there.
Uh, if these hit me, I'm gonna start floating.
Which is not nice.
Oh, I should probably have one of these...
in the chamber, you know?
Oh, I almost ate that.
And rods, I want these...
for things.
Oh, wait a minute.
I have a...
I forget the name of it now.
Silksong.
Silk touch.
So I can just take the glass.
Gimme.
Okay, keep going up.
See, the problem with my situation now is that I can't eat.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Imagine.
I could have died.
How am I so bad at this?
Come on.
Get up there.
Oh shit.
Okay, so this is the problem.
We have to remove this.
Now.
Oh, this did nothing.
Useless.
At least I'm getting a bunch of materials.
In fact, I'm getting all these rods.
Who knows what I can use them for later.
Good.
And then I'm gonna eat this.
This is some terrible food.
Definitely no substitute for a nice juicy steak and taters.
Let's just eat it for a bit here.
Get our HP up.
Now, where did I come from?
We may need to find a way to more easily see the direction we came from here.
It's not quite working out.
Like a beacon.
But not in the literal sense in this game, but you know.
Okay.
Got some more rods.
I think I got enough exotic materials here.
I was honestly hoping that something crazy would unlock, you know.
Something new that I can use for trains.
But it's okay.
I think I'm actually just gonna leave right now.
This is all I was curious about.
Where did I come from?
I'm also kind of scared.
Because I have all the good stuff on me, you know.
And I don't have any food.
I think the wise choice is to go back.
In fact, I see my exit over there.
If that is even the one I came through.
Could be a different one.
But nah, it's gotta be right.
Yep, I see bridges.
Something I wonder though.
Let's say I fall from a great height.
Like really far, you know.
And right before I hit the ground, I eat one of these fruits.
I do wonder if that will save me.
Like we're talking worst case scenario.
I have no other options.
You know.
Would be cool to try.
I'm gonna go slow.
I don't want to accidentally fall.
I even have my hands off A and D right now.
I only have W selected.
Because my keyboard is like a whole effect keyboard.
And just the slightest touch on the buttons.
Will make me step off, you know.
Scary stuff.
Oh, sir.
Will you move away from me?
You know what?
I'm just gonna go up.
Fuck it.
Oh, I ran out.
A little bit.
Wait, what?
Okay.
What's happening?
Okay, we're good.
Oh my god, man.
I thought we were gonna die.
I'm so scared.
Jump through the damn portal.
Let's get the hell out of here.
I am on edge right now.
Huh?
Is that the last bed I slept in?
That's not true.
Is it?
I could've sworn I slept at home.
I guess we just go straight up.
Actually, yeah.
There's water, right?
We have a natural elevator.
Okay, these guys need to die right now.
I hate them.
Where are you even coming from?
What are you?
Disgusting...
Beasts of the night.
Every time I see them, I wanna call them Fischer.
Like a German word for like a little creature thingy.
Okay, go!
Speed!
Easy.
Boat waiting for us and everything.
Now where's the moon?
Wait, where's the moon?
Have you ever seen this?
There's no moon.
But I know where I am.
That's crazy.
Wow.
The moon is gone.
Maybe a bug.
Okay, so now the plan is...
I think we're gonna go into the nether immediately.
As soon as I come home...
We are gonna deploy the drilling machine in the nether and we are gonna find so much netherite.
It's gonna blow your socks off.
And you're gonna be left with no socks and it's gonna be disgusting.
Because it's raining outside.
Dude, I thought I saw the moon but it's just like little weird textures in my scope.
Doesn't it look like a moon right there?
So weird.
What happens if I eat this in the boat?
Huh.
Wait, what?
I go nowhere.
So that's like the safe spot.
Interesting.
So...
Whenever I want to eat and I'm on an adventure, like let's say I'm in the end, I plop down the boat and I just sit in that and eat my fruit and I won't go everywhere.
Genius!
So if I'm up in a tower, in the end, I plop down the boat and I feast like a maniac.
Another sick tech discovered.
No thanks, sir.
I'm gonna go around.
Can I one-shot?
Oh!
Oh, this boat is sick.
Can I one-shot?
No, but he's burning?
Oh wait, it's raining.
So maybe not because of that.
Okay, so it's not a one-shot, but maybe with the fire it is.
This should not be a one-shot.
I think creepers and zombies have the same amount of health.
Oh my god, can you hit?
Yeah, didn't die from it.
Too bad.
Dude, what if I were to play the game with my hand and my foot at the same time?
Imagine.
Leave me alone.
Get away from me.
Also, this new sword.
Wait, they do burn in the night!
Huh?
Why don't they go...
How come they're not taking fire damage when I shoot them with a bow?
The hell?
That's inconsistent.
Cooked meat, baby.
Wait, I'm confused.
I don't know where I am!
I gotta sleep.
So I can see the sun.
Okay.
This way.
Oh nice, thank god the rain stopped.
The rain is so aggressive in this game.
How about just a little rain sometimes?
Light shower, not this frickin' rainstorm every time.
Dude, I'm actually kinda lost.
Like, why is it so unfamiliar, all this?
Huh?
Where the fuck am I?
How did I just get so lost?
Oh no wait, I think I know where I am.
If this is the forest that burned, then I know where I am.
Oh yes it is.
I know where I am.
Cook my meat for me.
I'm actually gonna go grab this guy too.
I need all the steaks I can get.
Dude, I should make steaks and frites today.
Haven't had that in a while.
Just plain old steak.
And some taters, precious.
Good combo.
What
am I doing?!
Jesus!
I forgot how to interact with the interaction.
For a brief second there, wow.
How did that go so overall?
Damn!
Look at that beauty.
It's gonna stop.
And deposit.
Very nice.
I think I should make something up on here.
Like, if I make the airplane, and I will...
We're gonna need like a landing strip, you know?
Like an airport.
And maybe somewhere up there would be cool.
On a mountain.
You know like in real life they have these really remote landing strips in the jungle and shit?
That's what I want.
Okay.
We made it home.
We even got some steaks.
Time to dig up the, well, drilling machine.
Drill, drill, drill.
Let me also deposit my exotics.
This is all exotic.
No, this one is not exotic.
I only got one shulker shell!
I should have gotten more.
But there weren't that many shulkers, so what can a man do, you know?
Leather is in here.
Actually, I would say end of pearls belong in here.
And this is construction.
And rods for sure.
What can I actually do with those I forgot?
Like, there's gotta be something that I can do.
Purpur pillar.
We can try to make that.
Who knows?
Maybe...
We should try and make a purpur slab.
Who knows?
Maybe that's the key to the whole puzzle.
Or maybe this...
Awww...
That's terrible.
I would also call it really bad luck that I only got one drop from them, you know?
And I killed like six or seven.
I swear to god, I wasn't trying to make a joke there.
It's just always...
Like, when you try to reach for like...
A number that isn't too low.
Not too high.
And you also don't wanna sound like you're precise.
It's six and seven!
That's like the most...
It's natural.
It is.
And...
Uh...
Wait.
Keep one stack.
Yup.
Now, in this...
We have the crank...
We don't actually need the crank.
What we need is all this.
And...
Didn't I...
That one!
Minecart contraption.
That's the one we need.
In fact, I think...
We have everything we need.
For this.
Don't need the water bucket, really.
Wood is essential.
Let me put that in...
This box here.
I'll keep the boat.
Fishing rod.
Let's...
Leave that here for now.
And now I think we're ready.
Let me just see.
So, uh...
Contraption controls...
Uh...
What was that?
Let me just see.
I had it next to the thing for a reason.
Mm-hmm.
So, if you put that on there...
You can use it to toggle them...
On and off.
Ah, yeah.
Smart.
Very cool.
Let's do that.
Anything else we need for the nether?
We got bow.
We got arrows.
Digging.
Essentials.
I think I'm ready.
Maybe go to bed first here.
In case I die, then I come back here at least.
There we go.
Let's go digging.
I assume everything's gonna work the same in the nether.
As it is everywhere else, regarding the physics and...
The machines and all that, you know?
I don't see why it shouldn't work, but who knows.
Okay, so what would be a good spot?
So here's the problem.
We need to find a good candidate spot that doesn't have a lot of lava.
Which is, you know, hard to find in the nether, because everything's frickin' lava in here.
But I'm thinking...
A good chunk of...
Uh...
This stuff, you know?
Preferably above the lava?
It's actually kinda scary.
Like, what if my shit falls in the lava, then it's gone, right?
Ooh, that's actually bad.
That's really bad.
Like, this right here could be good, you know?
Like, right there.
I think I'm gonna dig here.
Ooh, we dig fast!
Ooh!
I could also manually do it, I guess.
But, let's not do that.
Um, so it was three by three.
Let's start with that.
Let me just get this going here.
Like that.
And we needed this one.
I remember everything.
And we needed that.
Oh, shit.
You trying to mess with me?
I'm working here!
Ooh, get one shot, nerd.
Feels good to have a proper bow again, doesn't it?
Uh, wait.
Is it act...
No wait, it's not active now.
But if I...
Lock rotation.
Oh, I need to make sure everything is fine.
This one is using cobblestone now.
Is that a problem?
These are empty?
Yeah.
Okay.
Are you fighting me?!
Why are you fighting me?!
What did I do?!
You asshole!
Are we friends?
Are we good?
What the hell?!
Maybe he doesn't like me using...
My industrialization here.
Okay, you know what?
You're gonna die.
Fuck you.
Roasted pig.
In fact, maybe I'll have a roast pork tonight.
And frites.
Here we go!
Dick for the me!
It's working.
We just...
Hold on, we need to make sure.
Oh god, how do I...
I need to be fast to stop this thing.
Oh, wait, wait!
It doesn't have blocks!
Wait, what?
What?
It does have blocks.
I just can't see them for some reason.
I'm actually not sure what's happening here right now.
Wait, what's happening?!
Oh, you ran out of rail?
There you go.
You can have this...
Oh, you had 64 already.
Hmm...
That's fine.
Go!
Dick!
Dick for the me!
Oh, no!
What's happening?!
Oh, no.
Come on.
There we go, there we go, there we go.
We're back in business.
Back in business.
Now, obviously, we gotta remove these.
I'm also gonna take that, and this one.
Oh, it made a bridge!
Look at that!
That's so scary.
Is there gonna be lava?
No?
Okay, maybe it's okay.
We gotta refill this with some more tracks.
Dude, I don't even...
This is not even faster than digging manually.
Because I can...
You know?
I mean, the good thing about this is that it's collecting the items.
That's the good thing here.
That's the really good thing.
The one big advantage.
I should also be careful of accidentally destroying these.
There you go.
Keep going, keep going.
Can I use something else to destroy this?
Okay, we need to stop!
That's scary!
Stop!
I'm afraid of going out there.
We're gonna leave that one.
Uh...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How am I gonna...
How am I gonna retrieve that?
Without causing a ruckus?
Hey, asshole!
No!
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Is that the...
Oh, it's the same, look.
No, wait, no, wait, what?
Yeah, experience.
So this is where I have been.
Good.
Uh, we need to stop you right now.
Go back.
Come back to me, come back to me.
And then...
Lovely!
Now, uh, I need to experiment with this thing as well.
And then we need glue.
There we go.
So...
This one should just activate it and deactivate it, I guess.
Right?
So if I click this...
Wait, targeted...
Comp...
Component?
What?
Wait, it's on now, or...?
I'm actually not sure what this does.
Wait, this needed to be here, I think.
I forgot how to take this with me.
I needed...
That, I believe.
Does it need to be on?
Okay, now it's on.
Whoops!
I did something I shouldn't have done!
What did I do?
I just did something!
Huh?!
Get rid of this.
Oh no!
Yeah, okay, this is good.
Did I switch something back here?
There we go!
We got it, we got it.
Okay.
Needed to be off the thing.
Uh, yeah, so...
I'm gonna be honest here.
The digging machine...
As it stands right now in its current design...
Does not actually yield...
That much more progress than just doing it manually.
You know?
It's gonna really pay off though, if we make a machine that is like...
Omega massive.
Something with like a...
50 by 50 cross section.
You know?
Imagine that.
Or even just...
A 2 by 50.
We're fine.
My goodness.
Yeah, I should have known this was a bad idea to dig here.
I think I need to go further down and dig.
To be honest.
Also, I did some calculations back then, remember?
On, uh...
How far down to go to find this stuff?
And I...
Don't remember.
But it was...
Honestly, I have no idea.
I did something.
I tried to figure something out.
Uh...
This is a lot of lava.
So that's bad.
I don't know where to dig!
Let's just find a safe way down, shall we?
I'm gonna go back here again.
So we don't get lost.
Also, we don't need this on us.
Oh, you went into the lava, you silly.
He's making baking...
Bacon all on his own.
Could go down here.
We could make a little natural staircase, sort of.
Actually, even better.
Check it out.
Oh, why didn't I think of this?
Of course.
We're gonna do the following.
This is what I can do.
Because we're playing Minecraft.
Just dig!
It's that simple.
I'm digging a 2x2.
Because I'm also looking for netherite at the same time, you know?
So I'm being extra efficient.
What's up, guys?
Let's just go as far down as we can right now.
Oh!
Now I remember!
I went as far down as I could, and then I counted up.
Remember?
And it wasn't that far off from the very bottom.
That's the way I did that.
But it was kind of inconclusive.
Kinda just wanna start digging here, honestly.
I hate the silk touch!
Ugh!
What a pain!
Okay!
Yeah, that's bad.
So I guess we're...
fucked.
Pretty much.
I'm just gonna dig this way now.
Oh no!
Lava everywhere!
Is it really gonna be lava in every direction?
Shit.
Okay, well now we know this is a no-go.
Oh, wait a sec!
Nether quartz ore?
I wonder...
Yeah!
Nice!
We can blast the shit out of it in bulk!
I was thinking to myself, Oh, I'm gonna have to replace this in the world and mine it again.
You know?
But no!
Not today!
I'm gonna go over here now and then start digging down again.
Yeah, this tunnel I made there, I actually kinda like it.
But I'm gonna go that way instead.
Isn't that more prom- Not really.
I don't like this nether...
Area.
It is bad.
Let's just go down like this now.
Oy, oy, oy.
I am gonna have an emergency...
I was about to say pearl, but I don't have that.
Damn.
Oh crap.
No emergency pearls.
Okay, I don't like this tunnel.
I'm gonna find the perfect spot for this.
Maybe over here.
I believe.
This is the one.
I'm going a little slow on purpose because I'm so super afraid of dying with all this enchanted gear.
Ooh, no, no, no, no, no.
Cut that off.
Cut it out.
Oh!
Wait, this is the fortress.
Somehow, I made my way into the fortress.
I'm just gonna go random directions.
Stop!
Wow, that keeps going forever.
Whatever.
I am a little afraid.
I do wonder.
If I blast this, will I get the experience?
Maybe the act of mining it is the one thing that gives me the experience.
Oh!
Skeletons.
Black skeletons.
Dude, is it just me, or is this nether area, like, terrible?
What the hell?
Fine.
I will murder you.
Also, this is prime area to get lost in.
Shit, man.
Hmm.
I don't know where to go!
I'm like the opposite of a nether expert.
Maybe...
this way.
I've tried three directions now.
I mean, it does look kinda solid down there.
If I get down there, that could potentially be the thing.
The problem is, we gotta get back up at some point.
So, how do we do that?
I just wanna put some markers here, in case I get lost downstairs.
I need to see it.
In fact, why not do it like this, then?
I'm gonna go down!
Wish me luck.
My stomach...
makes my stomach churn.
So, like, over here, for example, that could be a spot for digging.
Like, right here!
Here.
This is it.
Except I hate...
this soul sand.
No lava yet?
Still so confused by the presence of this gravel here.
In the nether.
I mean, shouldn't we...
Aren't we at the lava level right now?
So, I think we're good.
I mean, this means we are below the lava.
Oh, I thought I just found it, man!
Yeah, that's not it.
Just had to double confirm.
Let's see...
Ooh!
No.
I forgot what it looks like, even.
But I'll know it when I see it.
Oh!
Oh, wait!
We're at the bottom!
Let's just start digging...
Oh, wait, we can't...
Let's just go a little further up like this.
This is what I did.
And then I went...
Oh, I remember now.
I remember.
So, what I did...
I made tunnels like that.
Then I went up.
Made tunnels like that.
And then I...
That's how I found a lot.
Just doing that, you know?
So, that's what we're gonna do!
Isn't it grand?
Now, down here I could use the digging machine, maybe.
And, you know what?
Maybe there is a way to make it drive on its own, so I don't have to push it.
Especially now that we have this...
Uh...
Diesel...
Whatever.
Like the engine.
Portable engine.
Like, there's gotta be a way to do that.
And honestly, so far, this is good news.
Like, we haven't hit lava in a while.
This could be a solid spot for finding some netherite.
Imagine if there's a way to just see netherite through the walls with like something in Create, you know?
Like some goggles or something.
And I figure out about it after I get all my netherite.
I would be a little upsetty spaghetti.
If that is what's gonna end up happening.
Bro, there's nothing here!
I'm gonna go back.
Let's go a little higher.
But I do seem to remember it was kinda random.
Like, it doesn't really matter too much.
The main factor in finding a lot of netherite in my experience is that you have a spot where there's just as little lava as possible.
So, for example, right here.
This is the prime spot for it, you know?
One... so I would go like here.
Oh, I got fooled!
I really thought.
It's gotta be like something new we can make with netherite, right?
Yeah, this... this gravel is pissing me off.
When has gravel ever been good?
It only causes frustration.
I don't think I should be afraid of falling into lava.
Because I'm so far down that...
that can't be lava below me.
At least not a lot.
Oh man, this is... there's nothing here.
Okay, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna...
to waste... or to save a bit of time.
I'm gonna go up one.
Let me see here.
What's the best way to do this?
Up here.
That way we're gonna come back to the...
staircase we made from the other side.
Shit, shit.
Maybe just a small pocket of lava?
Yep.
I guess that can happen.
I should end up at the staircase.
Beautiful.
Look at that.
Wonderful.
Man.
I wanna set the machine loose again.
I wanna... okay, here's what we're gonna do.
Fuck, man.
It's not efficient!
Pain!
Let me stick to one side for now.
I gotta find some at some point here.
Oh my god, I'm getting sick.
It's like staring into one of those...
optical illusions for too long, you know?
And your brain starts to melt.
That's what I'm seeing right now.
Why is this shit so rare, man?
Like, holy crap.
Have I ever found more than, like, 15 in my entire life playing this game?
I don't think I have.
It is unbelievably rare.
Let's go a little higher.
Let's just try...
Maybe near this level here, with this stuff.
Maybe that will do something.
Maybe an indicator.
I'm glad I can at least destroy these sort of fast.
Why is there so much of that?
Well, okay, it does seem like if you're too far down, you're not gonna find even this stuff, right?
But now that we've gone a little further up, we find more of, uh...
Of the experience-giving blocks here.
What are they called again?
Quartz, right?
Could just be placebo.
Or whatchamacallit.
Confirmation bias.
Ah...
I don't like this.
Let's go the other way.
This way.
Honestly, it's kinda pretty walking through these...
How come I'm not taking damage touching these?
I thought they hurt.
Get rid of that.
Dude, all I want is one.
Just one.
And I'm happy.
It's honestly more of a test of just, what will I unlock with that one piece, you know?
More than anything else.
Okay, so that's lava, we don't go that way.
Now we're gonna do this.
Here, we're gonna dig that way.
Full sense.
Oh, I like this song.
It's a nice song.
It's fitting.
It's like...
Very lonely song.
Lost in some dimension.
All alone in the world, you know?
You know there's no one else.
It's just you and these weird AI cows and sheep and weird skeletons that have no brains.
Just mindlessly wandering around, you know?
Imagine being the guy.
In this game.
Man, that would suck, actually.
Okay, so you do...
It's only when you stand on it.
Fuck.
I thought when you touched it from the side, it would also damage you.
Ah.
See, I don't like that.
So, I'm just gonna go off...
Script here.
Oh, no, wait.
I'm back here now?
Oh, man.
How come I haven't found one yet?
We're almost at half durability on this fucking pickaxe.
That's crazy.
Where's the staircase at?
Oh, my God.
Did I miss it?
Uh, what?
Where the hell am I?
Ah, whatever.
Keep digging.
Slow descent into madness here.
Like a kaleidoscope in front of me.
But without colors.
Just one color.
Maybe, like, three.
That's the best description I can give of this right here.
Show me the netherite!
I gotta squint at the screen.
I'm just seeing shapes and colors right now.
Like, there's no...
There's nothing.
Oh, God!
I didn't even, like, react properly there.
Like, that was on instinct.
And I have no...
Like, where is the staircase?
It's crazy.
Is it here?
No?
I wanna get off.
I wanna get out.
I'm starting to feel claustrophobic in here.
Here we are.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
It's not actually that bad.
We're kinda close to the top.
Let's try somewhere in between.
Maybe here.
I'm taking, uh...
Samples, you know?
Stickpröver.
There's a word for that in English.
Okay, at least I get this.
I mean, this is gonna be a nice payday in terms of experience later.
So, you know.
It's not all bad.
Even if I lose, I kinda win.
Although not really.
At least I found a nice spot to dig.
Holy shit!
That's crazy.
Did the sound just play because of that?
Did you hear that?
A special sound just played.
Okay, you know what?
I feel motivated.
Keep going, man.
We found... we found it.
Now we just gotta...
Let me... let me go the other direction then.
No, actually, where did I find this?
Let me actually dig around this.
I just wanna see.
Maybe there's more.
Maybe they cluster a little bit, you know?
Oh man, it's not looking like...
Damn.
Okay, well...
We got one!
That makes it already worth it.
I'm just so happy that I got one.
But, I mean, I'm a little greedy now.
I want more.
We can't just stop at one.
Let me go this way.
Mmm, yeah.
Get rid of that.
Oh, that's lava.
Is it though lava fully?
No, it's just a pocket.
Okay, just a pocket of lava.
No problem.
Hate the gravel, man!
That's something a digging machine is pretty good at fixing.
Oh my god, stop!
Why won't it stop?
Okay, I guess we don't go that way.
Let me do this.
Man, stop burning!
That took forever.
Should have worn the copper back tank.
Like, who knows?
Maybe there's like a rule where...
Ancient debris spawns more closely to other things.
Like, for example, the quartz.
So if I find this, maybe I should be like, oh, what else is here?
You know what I mean?
But I have yet to see any evidence.
I'm just speaking.
Oh, that way.
So this way.
Blackstone.
Maybe there is no rhyme or reason to this, you know?
And I'm just freaking making shit up.
I mean, one thing we can confirm.
It can only be found in the nether.
And so far at least, always in...
Nether Rack.
Forgot the name.
And we're lavaing.
That means we're not gonna do that anymore.
Maybe I'll stop at two.
I can stop at any time.
It's funny how this was like...
Horrible.
Before, you know?
And then as soon as I found the ancient debris, I'm like, okay, this is sick.
I wanna keep digging.
It's weird how the brain works.
Oh, man.
I guess that's what's...
Making people, and myself included, at least, before I started doing this.
Be like, oh man, I hate this job, you know?
Then you get the paycheck and you're like, fuck yeah, man.
Nice, let's keep going.
Let's keep working, you know?
Uh, wait, not that way.
Let's go like...
There's, there's, honestly, I'm kinda fucking around.
There's no real...
Systematics to this.
Oh, crap.
All I'm doing right now is staying on this level.
Because I found one.
So my brain is telling me, keep going here, you know?
I do wonder though, hold on.
Im...
Like, I'm starting to think.
If you...
If you put physics on something...
Uh...
For example...
If I put ancient debris in lava...
I wonder if that will break.
Or if it'll just float.
Because what you could do...
Imagine this, okay?
Remember when I told you about stealing a hotel?
Like, putting it in my pocket and just walking off with it?
Imagine I take a...
Fucking thousand by thousand...
Block.
Of blocks.
In the world.
You know?
And I simulate it.
And I let it all fall into lava.
And maybe...
All that survives...
Is the ancient debris.
Do you, do you see where I'm going with this?
I'm basically taking an entire area.
And letting it fall into lava.
So like...
Thousand by thousand, you know?
That would be...
Well, a million.
So a million blocks.
Statistically, how many ancient debris would be in there?
Probably about one.
In my experience, I don't know, man.
It does feel like that sometimes though, right?
It's probably more than one.
But I wonder if it's possible.
And...
I'm gonna try and throw my ancient debris into lava.
I hate...
It's an experiment.
I gotta try it, man.
I gotta see if it works.
I'm getting some crazy ideas now.
I'm starting to think with create, you know?
I guess for that to work, I would have to go to the top left corner of this...
Well, massive...
block selection and then go to the bottom right corner.
And then, you know, it'll all...
Although, do the...
Does the glue go all that way?
Hmm.
I wonder.
Maybe not.
Maybe there's a limit to how much you can glue.
Oh, shit.
Bop!
Block it!
Oh, no!
I'm starting to hit a lot of lava for some reason.
Don't like that.
Why are you always lava?
Oh, my God.
Stop fucking lava.
God, this is terrible.
Get me out of this.
Come on.
One more ancient debris just for the road.
One ancient debris for the lava.
One for my tummy.
Also, I'm...
I'm running out of durability here.
Like, we...
There's a world where we don't find this before this axe breaks.
And there's definitely a world where we don't find it before my heart breaks.
Oh, terrible.
I mean, okay.
Oh, I was fast.
Like lightning.
It's like I knew.
That way...
Come on!
Uno mas, uno mas, uno mas.
Guys, I find another one within five minutes.
Five minutes.
Starting now.
Dude, I need to use my foot.
This is like the perfect foot situation.
Doing stuff like this?
Oh yeah.
Oh shit!
Oh my god.
Stop!
Why does it feel like I'm running out of options?
Durability is very low!
Wow, this is...
Some fast digging.
Come on, where are you?
I don't understand.
The script says I'm supposed to find my second one...
Like now.
Why isn't it happening?
Okay, now I actually kind of love the gravel because...
It means I don't waste durability on my pickaxe.
A single...
Rare...
Gravel W.
Okay, you know what?
Crazy idea.
Uh...
No.
No crazy ideas.
Do we frustrate mining?
Frustrate mining.
Frustration mining.
Come on!
Show it!
Don't do this to me!
Okay, you know what?
There's a way out of this.
Not like that, not like that, not like that.
I am not leaving without my second one.
You know what that means?
We're bringing out the machine.
It's happening.
Time to dig.
I can't break my thing.
Nice.
Okay, now.
Lock that shit.
Dig for me!
Yeah!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hey, I wonder if it gets stuck on ancient debris?
What if it finds it?
Is it gonna just put it in the box?
Or...
Is it gonna stop digging?
I don't know.
I... hmm.
Nah, it's probably just gonna...
I don't know, actually.
Come on, come on, come on.
Now we gotta clean this up.
Nice, we almost ran out there.
Let's give you some more of this juice.
More speed!
Speed!
Okay, maybe this is faster, actually.
Hey, you know what?
I like this more than I did the manual digging.
This is... this is good!
Yo, this is it!
I believe, I believe, I believe!
Do you believe?
Faster!
It also... it's also taking a bigger surface area every time, you know?
Like, it allows me to search a bigger area.
We just... we just gotta stop it in time, if shit happens, you know?
Hey, wait, if shit happens, I just do, uh...
this.
Shit!
Happened!
I accidentally left-clicked!
I should've right-clicked!
Oh, man.
Wow.
It's fine, though.
Wait!
Oh, it's there.
Is it, uh... this is... wait, what?
Okay.
Push it.
Okay, we're fine, we're fine.
Whew.
So, from now on, as soon as shit happens, I pull out my...
I was about to say schlong.
I pull out this thing!
And I right-click the mother...
And then, and then everything's fine.
Out of here!
I'm out of here!
Exactly like that!
That's how you do it, man!
Now, give me this.
We're gonna, we're gonna...
Uh, see, what, see, this is now a hazard.
So, I have determined...
We are gonna stop digging this way.
We're now gonna go the other way.
So, I'm gonna go like that.
Like this.
Oh my god, my durability!
We can't be using...
No more.
You may not use that any more.
You're done.
Okay, now...
Here...
There...
And...
Boom!
Ready for the dick?
Dick for me!
Wait.
Uh, wait, hold on.
There we go, lock that rotation.
Go!
Ah!
Wait, I misaligned it.
Whoops.
Take it back.
Oh no, I need my pickaxe!
I don't.
We're chilling.
Uh, three by threes.
I mean...
Here.
There.
And...
Lock the rotation.
Push!
It's gonna be a pain to remove these tracks though.
Oh no, this is gonna be really annoying.
Actually, ideally, I would be digging one more to the right.
You know?
But it's fine.
It's deployed.
It's going.
We're gonna leave it.
I'm also gonna give it some more of this.
There you go.
Some more tracks as well, sire.
Tracks, me lord.
Wait, I need to make a little shitty pickaxe, actually.
I need, I need blackstone.
Oh no.
Oh, and you know, it probably has blackstone in the, in the box.
Yeah, yeah, this is not gonna work out.
So what we're gonna do now is this.
Boop!
Like that.
We're gonna go back that way.
Oops, not too far, not too far.
That's good.
I can't open that, so I need to do this.
Blackstone, we're gonna make a little pickaxe here.
Oh, I also had cobblestone.
Oh, didn't even see that.
Make two of them.
There we go.
Nice!
Not bad, eh?
Thinking on my feet here.
Because now we can remove these with ease.
And there's less chance of breaking through the floor and fucking ourselves over.
It's fantastic.
Something so satisfying about- Yo, isn't it super satisfying to dig like this?
Look at this massive area we've dug through in like, almost no time.
It's incredible.
Okay, uh, lock that shit.
Go!
Keep digging!
Look at the speed!
Wow!
Why was it so fast?
I can barely catch up with it!
Show me the ancient debris!
I can feel it, it's here.
It's even making experience for me!
This is the best day ever.
There you go!
You need more of this?
I got you!
I got you, bro!
Okay, digging machine is back on the menu, boys.
This is, this is the life.
Holy shit.
Why are you so slow?
Come on!
Move it!
Who knows?
Maybe there's like, already ancient debris inside the boxes.
Oh, the best part?
It's going through this like, like it's warm butter.
More tracks, me lord!
Faster!
Oh!
What is it digging through?
You hear that?
That's a special material that just got ducked through.
Not fast enough!
Also, I gotta be ready to disassemble it if something happens.
As soon as lava comes...
And we got it.
Faster!
There we go.
That's more like it.
Hell yeah, dude!
Dude, the, the, the railroad tracks kind of prevent lava from flowing.
I didn't know that was a...
Oh!
My heart sank for a moment!
It was just the stone pancakes!
Oh ho ho!
Man!
That was scary!
Wow!
Okay!
Okay, we're gonna dig this way now.
I have determined it, so... Track me this way.
And then... Where did I put my thing?
Wait, what?
Did I leave it behind back here?
It's possible that I did.
Wait a sec.
Oh my god, I did!
Thank god I came back for this!
Jesus!
That was scary.
Hi, look at this!
This is just sad remains of the times I did the frustrating mining.
Those days are over.
From now on, we're doing the best mining of all time.
And you know what?
There may already be ancient debris inside this box.
Shall we check?
Should I check?
No.
You know what?
I'm gonna wait a bit more.
I'm not ready to check yet.
I'm gonna wait until I have... a million.
I'm not gonna check yet.
I'm not gonna wait.
Okay, let's see here.
Four rails.
Let's give this some more juice like that.
No!
Destroy that.
Lock it!
Go!
Hello?
Speed, maybe?
Huh?
Oh shit.
What's happening?
Something ain't right here.
What did I do wrong?
Turn it off first.
There.
On.
Go.
Huh?
Oh, is it just because of this?
Or... Ah, okay.
Nice.
Good.
Oh shit.
No!
Not already!
Oh, that's horrible.
Alright.
Uh, fine.
We're not gonna go that way.
Bad idea.
We're gonna go this way instead.
We're gonna go back where we came from.
And I will, um... Hmm.
Questions, questions.
Should I... Do it, uh, the efficient way or the nice way?
I think I'll take the nice way.
Okay.
I'm gonna do... I'm gonna do... One, two, three.
And... There.
There.
And then... Oh my god!
That was a loud noise!
What the fuck?
Lock it.
Oh!
Wait!
Uh... I can't use my pickaxe!
It's gonna break!
Guys!
Do I gamble it?
Do I... Do I do the one... The one dig?
The one dig?
Do we... Do one dig?
I'm gonna do one dig?
I'm gonna do one dig.
Never again shall we use this pickaxe.
Oh my god!
Oh, that was scary!
Wait, wait, wait.
Uh, give me my other pickaxe?
I can't believe I almost missed this!
This is literally the meme of the guy mining, you know, and stopping right before the...
Uh, you know, the... The goodies!
Oh shit.
Okay.
Okay, man!
Sick!
Uh, wait, what was I doing?
Right.
Go!
I am so...
Wait, why does it stop?
Uh... Actually, I have an idea.
I have a theory on how to make this faster.
Check it out.
We start with the thing back here.
We activate...
I kinda...
I messed it up there, but the idea is to push this with a lot of speed into it.
So that momentum, uh, transfers.
It doesn't make sense physically or logically, but you know.
It is Minecraft.
So who knows.
Let's see here.
We got 19 rails.
That means we still have a bunch to go.
Let me switch this out.
What happened there?
Was that me?
Did I do that?
Oh, I accidentally replaced it.
I see what happened.
Go!
Ah, damn.
What do I do with them?
Speed!
God, this is so satisfying.
Imagine if it's picking up all kinds of ancient debris in its box.
I can't wait to see this box when it's done.
And I guess we'll know when it's full, when it starts dropping these things on the floor.
Right?
Keep going!
Look at the way it's dismantling all that.
Oh, yeah.
This is so much fucking fun, dude.
I love the...
The best part is, this is just the start of the digging machine.
Like, this will be so much better.
I'm gonna make this incredible down the line.
We're just in the primitive stages right now.
We're gonna...
We're gonna make a freaking...
massive machine.
On a biblical level, you know?
Oh, shit!
We're digging nothing now.
Uh, stop then.
Questions!
Uh, let's go here.
I like that.
Dut, dut, dut!
Let's see how fast I can do this.
So we got...
Wait, did I lose the thing again?
No, it's here.
That's...
And then the idea now is to do the following.
I mean, uh...
Okay.
It's fine.
Oh, this needs to go.
Yeah, this is the problem.
Oh, wait!
Wait, that's part of the machine, isn't it?
Dude.
I just got so scared.
Okay, keep digging.
Everything's fine.
Uh, let's make another pickaxe.
Woo!
Scary stuff.
There we go.
Why did it stop?
Stop stopping!
I need you to go!
Why won't you just be normal?
Oh!
I think you ran out.
So did you, I think.
No, you didn't.
We're Gucci.
Hello!
Oh, what the...
Oh my god, skeletons are spawning now, too.
So, I think it's gonna start digging slowly if it finds ancient debris.
Dude, look at that.
Ooh, that's satisfying to look at from a profile, isn't it?
I need to remove these.
I can't believe I wasted all my durability trying to dig manually down here.
I should have thought that the machine would be better.
Like, what is wrong with me?
We have industrialization at our fingertips, and I'm going in there with a spoon, you know?
Thinking, this is it!
This is the way!
Like, not only is the spoon terrible, it's also breaking my back from all the hard work, you know?
I'm starting to fucking see kaleidoscopes and shit.
No more...
No more kaleidoscopes!
We're done with that.
Is there...
No.
Oh, whoa!
What's happening?
Okay, it's just that.
Okay.
Let me replace...
Milord.
Oh, wait!
There's lava here!
Lava here!
I think.
Get ready.
No?
What?
Did my machine destroy the lava?
How did that work?
You heard the psst, and then it's gone.
I got two ancient debris already.
Let's do one more that way.
Let's just do one more line.
I can stop any time.
Oh, actually!
I can, but I'm not gonna, because...
I mean, I am gonna, but I'm gonna come back with a bigger machine right after this.
I'm gonna...
Decimate the nether!
Here.
Lock!
Destroy this!
Oh, no.
Did I already mess it up?
What happened?
What have I done?
Come on.
Oh, no!
Why is it doing this?
Please?
Oh, it's always when you start it up.
Something is wrong, you know, because of this.
Yeah, you always gotta remember that.
That's actually...
That's right.
Makes sense.
And...
Go!
You glorious bastard.
Oh, this track is so good, too.
Oh, wait.
You need a refuel?
There you go.
Any more tracks, sire?
Faster.
Oh, you know what?
I'm going to come back with a self-driving version.
Why am I inventing a steam engine and then manually cranking it?
That's dumb.
We have to, we have to, we have to make this as best as it can be.
What?
Did you see that?
It did something just now.
And when I say saw, I meant heard.
Faster, faster, faster.
And there you go.
Have fun.
Oh, I thought this was ancient debris.
I got fooled.
They fooled me.
Did he get picked up?
Is it in there?
Oh, my God.
Maybe we got more in there.
This is amazing.
There you go.
Keep digging, keep digging.
The hell was that sound?
There's like a bass line.
Bass in my ear.
Whoa, whoa.
It's happening.
It's digging.
It's a debris.
I think that was an ancient debris.
Yeah.
How many am I getting?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Throw away some stuff that I don't need.
I don't need this shit.
I don't need this either.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, man.
Oh.
Guys, I'm not going to stop yet.
We're going to keep going.
It's going to be the most insane thing ever.
Oh, yeah, you're running out.
There you go.
Oh, that was a close one.
Shit.
Grab it.
We're out of here.
No, we're not.
Kidding.
I'm going to make spoons.
Manuals.
Like that.
And then...
There's got to be a better way to do that.
How do I evenly...
There you go.
And then...
Oh, yeah.
Four pickaxes.
And four colossus.
Wow, lava everywhere.
Will you stop that?
Maybe.
Are you done?
You're not even done.
Oh, my goodness.
Huh?
Okay, we're not going that way.
Fuck that crap.
That just gave me an aneurysm.
What I will do, however...
I will...
I will do another line.
Just one more.
That's fine.
Dude, this turned from tedious as fuck...
To the best thing in the universe.
There.
But wait, now it should be...
Dis...
There we go.
Locked.
It's locked.
Go!
My sweet prince.
Ah, it's always in the beginning.
We got to jumpstart it.
There we go.
You have been jumpstarted.
And now...
Oh, no.
Oh, stop!
It's going buck wild!
Freaking digging machines gone wild here.
We don't want none of that.
Okay, let's do this properly.
I think when we do a line from now on, we're going to have to make a little bit of a preemptive...
You know.
You know what I mean.
Don't you?
Phew.
There.
But...
Actually, don't activate yet.
Put this there.
Lock, rotation, boom, and...
Speed!
And we should be good.
How many do I possess?
18 plus 11 is 29, I guess.
But I don't trust the game on that.
It's digging experience for me, which is amazing.
Yo, that could be like...
An experience machine, in a way.
Ah...
Would it, though?
Doesn't the experience disappear after a while?
I'm not actually sure if it does.
It must disappear, right?
Keep digging.
See, that's what I'm talking...
That's the speed right there.
Faster.
Oh, skeletons!
Wait!
Is he gonna die?
What if he walks into the machine?
Ah, but he's not gonna walk through the wall, though, so...
Will it even happen?
Oh, you bastard!
Got him.
Dude, I get a mini heart attack every time.
Oh, why did it...
Wait, are we full?
We may be full.
Guys, we're gonna check now.
Okay.
Prediction time.
Is it gonna be more...
...or less than two?
I think it's going to be...
...exactly two.
It's gonna be two.
Okay, that's fine.
Here we go.
But, wait, I saw it!
I saw it!
Oh.
Wait, why was that not picked up, though?
Hold on a minute now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why was that not picked up?
I mean, the...
Was it full?
The inventory wasn't full.
Wait.
Something's off here.
What's happening?
What's going on?
I'm gonna throw away some of this.
I think maybe...
Okay, maybe the inventory was just full.
Throw this away, too.
What?
Okay.
Uh, let's do one more.
I just want one more ancient debris.
You know?
Uno mas.
That should be possible.
Lock that crap.
Grab this.
And push!
Oh, I don't want to pick this up.
Ah, whatever.
Maybe it does just drop it on the floor when it finds ancient debris.
I just don't understand why it would do that.
It doesn't make sense logically to me.
Why that would happen.
Uh-oh!
It probably ran out of...
Yeah...
Dang.
That's what happened.
Ah, shit.
Oh, no.
Don't circle.
I hate when it circularizes.
The other way, please.
But it's not locked rotation now.
It's...
It's weirdly wild.
But still controlled, you know?
Just like Jackie.
Man, that's kind of deep, if you think about it.
Technically a wild animal, but controlled.
I should be a philosopher.
Faster!
I do like when it's digging slow.
It means there's potentially some goodies.
That ain't good.
Actually, it's fine.
Wait a sec.
Wait a...
Wait a minute.
Oh, two things.
One.
It seemed like it was pushing the experience along as it went.
That's an interesting observation, I guess.
The other thing.
Couldn't we just...
Plop it down like this and just go?
My God!
That's so much easier.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
If this is lava, is it gone?
Oh, that's scary, man.
Damn,
son.
Wow.
Why can't I block it?
Oh, wait.
I don't have any food.
Stupid lava.
Alright, whatever.
Wait, I have no food!
I think it's time to leave!
One more line.
Uno mas.
One last.
One more.
Ah, but the problem is, it's not gonna be locked, I guess, then.
Also, I just messed it up.
We should put this, uh, somewhere else.
In the back, like that.
No, that's also too... Okay, I see how it is.
I get it.
Oh, no!
Yes!
That's how we do it.
This is how we do it.
Boop!
Oh, we have to take care of those guys back there.
Oh, wait, this is actually kind of dangerous.
Ooh, I'm scared.
Oh, you ran out?
Aw, crap.
Go.
Oh, no!
Man.
I do hate that.
Hey, do I just need one?
Wait, did I just optimize it even more?
Check this out.
Uno.
Ah, not really.
It needs at least two.
Otherwise, it's gonna go crazy.
I see how it is.
Yeah.
Always two.
Sweet spot is two.
Beautiful.
We cannot sprint, by the way.
Oh, wait a minute.
These are friendlies.
I almost just killed them.
Hold on.
Someone's calling me.
Never mind.
It's a spam number.
Uh, what if the pigs are getting shredded?
Orphan shredder?
Mobile orphan shredder.
Moss.
Wait, it's moss.
Come on.
One more ancient.
For the road.
Oh, fuck.
My heart sinks into my stomach.
Every time.
I cry every time.
Really should be checking the walls and ceiling as well, by the way.
Just in case.
Will you get out of the way, please, sir?
Come on.
Speed.
Imagine I anger the... Oi.
Oh, I thought we found it.
Imagine we anger these pigs down here right now.
That would be disastrous.
Wouldn't it?
We're not fast enough.
Faster.
Man, I did find the perfect digging spot, though.
You can't say I didn't.
This is the spot.
Of all spots for this.
Come on, man.
It's a little too slow.
I'm trying to think.
How would I even speed this up?
Like, okay, let's say we put the... the portable engine or whatever.
How does it even... like, how would that even work?
I don't understand how that would...
affect it.
It just...
Maybe... Hmm.
I don't actually see a way to do that.
Now that I think about it.
Because don't you need a...
Like, it's turning a crank.
And...
Yeah, well.
There's many issues with that.
Just from a mental perspective right now.
Come on.
Oh!
We're leaving.
Hmm.
Uh...
Let me check the thing.
Who knows?
Man, nothing?
That...
Wow, it gets filled up fast here.
That's a...
That's a lot.
Wow.
Oh, I guess I'm footing now.
Okay.
Bro, I don't understand shit.
Oh, no.
Why the...
What...
What just even happened?
I don't understand!
Like, it's so stupid!
Like, did...
That was a bug!
I just died to a bug.
Thank you, game.
Great.
Fantastic.
That doesn't make any sense at all.
Give me sweet berries.
Crying out loud.
There.
I got some sweet berries.
Like, what even was that?
Died in a...
What was it?
Suffocated in a wall!
Alright.
What do you think about that, Jimothy?
That's some bullshit, ain't it?
I think it is.
And now I'm footing it!
Okay, so it's this way.
And the problem is, we're on foot now.
Literally.
Like, I can't aim for shit right now.
I think I went this way.
Wait, how...
Did I just fall down?
Oh, fuck!
They're fighting each other!
Oh, my God.
Wait, how did I...
Oh, God!
No!
I'm gonna die!
Oh, the fucking...
I can't take this!
I can't stand...
Like, I don't understand why I just fucking suffocated in a wall out of nowhere and now I have to do this shit.
It makes no sense.
It makes no sense at all.
One arrow.
Yeah.
Chest piece.
Diamond chest plate.
Good.
Do I have food in the oven?
Oh, crap.
I can't aim with my foot, man.
Where were you?
Oh, right.
Netherite scrap.
Maybe an axe?
Maybe also, like...
We need food.
Let's cook this.
There we go.
Oh, my God.
Also, why couldn't I jump down?
Like, there must be a spot I could have jumped down.
Oh, let me make...
This actually...
This is great.
Bread.
Eight.
Oh, that's actually nice.
Okay.
We don't have to panic.
It's just...
Annoying to die in a wall out of nowhere.
That makes no sense at all, you know?
But shit happens, I guess.
Whatever.
That's what it is.
Oh, I can...
Let's just bring a boat, actually.
Oh, that's probably what it...
Yeah, that's what I did, actually.
I just fell down on a boat.
Um, I don't have a boat.
I have so many boats, and I keep throwing them away and leaving them in random spots, you know?
Uh, give me...
Sixteen.
I feel like you should be impressed at how well I'm playing with my foot right now.
You know what?
I'm gonna sleep.
Oh, yeah, the bow is shitty now.
Okay, calm down, calm down.
Uh, you know what?
We're actually on a timer.
We have to hurry.
This is timer.
The problem is...
It's a labyrinth down there.
I may not get my items, which is such...
Like, I can't even stand to think about that right now.
Nice.
Good hit.
Oh, shit!
Oh, it crashed.
What did I dig?
Oh, no.
I don't know where I dug!
Oh, oh.
It has to be it.
Uh...
This way?
Oh, god.
Oh, shit!
I lost all my shit!
It's all...
It's all gone.
There's no way I'm getting that back.
Okay, think.
Think.
Uh, I went down and I...
And I did something in between.
Uh, it's gotta be here.
Is that...
No, fuck!
Uh, down here.
Look at something that's big!
That doesn't look big at all!
Bro, it could be anywhere.
Anywhere.
Like...
Oh, no!
It's fucking over.
I can't...
Like, three netherites!
Fucking suffocating in a wall!
Look at that!
Here?
Come on.
Maybe?
I don't know.
I don't know what I did, man.
This ain't good.
I don't know where I'm going.
Just keep running.
How...
Is this big of an area so hard to miss?
Wait.
I'm going in circles!
It's...
It's gone.
It's gone!
I've noted where I am.
I can't...
I don't...
I don't understand what's going on!
Oh!
I...
I don't know!
I have no fucking clue!
Is it...
This way, maybe?
I...
No.
I give up.
It's gone.
I don't even want to try anymore.
Like, it's fucking over.
It's fucking over.
I tried that way.
I don't know.
I can't even fucking find the same spot.
That's insane to me.
Like, how is this big of an area fucking just...
Vanished?
It makes no sense.
It makes no sense at all.
It's not that one.
I have no idea where the hell this place is.
I'm out.
It's fine, though.
Let's elevate ourselves to a better mental state here.
And also a higher plane.
What's up, dude?
Now, I jumped from...
Wait.
Where did I...
I jumped from there!
So it's actually right up here.
We need some blocks.
I have a plan.
It's fine.
It's going to be...
A lot better.
I...
Like, I...
It feels so incredibly bad...
To die to something that...
For all intents and purposes...
Feels like a complete fucking bug.
Like, I don't know...
How the fuck...
In any dimension or world...
It makes sense...
To click on something...
And then somehow die...
Suffocating in a wall?
That doesn't make any sense to me.
But...
But okay.
Like, that's just straight up bullshit.
Like, it felt like I got teleported...
Into another...
Fucking dimension into...
Like, a wall.
Somewhere.
I have no idea...
How that makes any sense at all.
Now, where am I?
Ah, good.
Okay.
Alright.
Get me the hell out of here.
I have a mega plan, though.
And this has only fueled my hate for the nether even more.
We're gonna commit the ultimate genocide down there.
A genocide of blocks.
You'll see what I mean.
What do I need?
Alloys, ingots, casings.
So I need a million of each.
Thank you.
Okay.
Uh, we're gonna need these.
We don't have any iron, it seems.
Which is...
A real bummer.
Bro, I lost everything.
Everything.
All my tools.
Uh, where's this...
Huh?
Oh god, what was it called?
Wrench.
Cockwheel, stick, and sheets.
Cockwheel...
But I need a small one.
I guess we have...
Uh, yeah, we have these.
Nice.
And cockwheels are just made from...
This.
And some wood, I believe.
Let's just make all of it.
And sticks, I believe we have.
Okay, at least we have this one again.
That's good.
Now, the factory, uh...
We were producing and the side casings.
But it was also making...
The alloys.
Used for the casings.
So I will need to...
That just looks like a mess down there.
Look at that.
It's like everything is going in.
How do I do this in a better way?
I guess I can just put a chest here, right?
What's this chest for?
Get rid of that.
Oh, no, you're not.
Oh, wait.
I can't attack with my foot!
So weird.
There we go.
I figured it out.
Is that feeding into it?
Oh, my God.
Will you leave me alone?
Holy crap!
Where's my bed?
Didn't I have a bed here?
Ah, it seems to be gone.
Okay, this is not working.
What's an easy way to do this, man?
I guess maybe a funnel down below or...
Oh, my God.
Man, this is...
Oh, this is so depressing.
I forgot what needed to be in there.
Oh, my God.
These...
Pissants!
It feels like playing Terraria right now or something.
Go to bed.
Let's just fix the inventory first.
Oh, man.
This is rough.
I don't even know.
How would I even take things from that basin?
Is it just a hopper down below or what?
I have no idea.
I don't even have one.
I need a funnel.
And the side funnel.
Funnel into a chest, I guess, would be the way to do that.
So we have the belt.
We got some shafts.
Let me also replace this.
This bow is so bad.
I lost my incredible bow as well.
Man, it doesn't get worse than this.
This is, like, the worst thing that could have ever happened.
Three ancient debris.
And everything I had, man.
That's crazy to me.
That's probably the biggest loss I've ever had in this game.
I don't even see how anything else comes close.
Do we need a belt in between or what?
Bro, I...
I don't even have any clue how to fucking do this.
Like...
What?
I have no clue how to do this.
Give me the thing!
Oh my god.
Give me a hopper.
There's gotta be a hopper here somewhere.
A chute, maybe.
Let's shoot the shit out of this.
Chest.
Come on.
This better work.
Where the hell is the chest now?
I am losing my patience here.
It's just...
Wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Do we need to filter that or something?
Is there a filter thingy on it?
Wait.
These two are gonna make fucking alloys, right?
And this one says only alloys.
So why is it not pooping out alloys only?
I guess because it needs more...
anthocytes.
And to make anthocytes.
Gravel.
Right.
No, wait.
That wasn't it.
Mixing.
Oh, yeah.
Diorite.
I may have some.
But even if I have diorite and I make it work...
How come it was pooping out the nuggets?
Like, the filter was still there.
Shouldn't it have not pooped out anything?
Alloys.
I mean, I have 64 of them now.
It's not bad.
And I definitely have a lot of these.
Let me see here.
Drill.
Oh, yeah.
Iron.
The problem is, I don't have any iron, man.
Hey, I have 14 iron.
That's something.
The last thing I want to do right now is to go mine some iron.
It really is the last thing I want to do.
Um...
Diorite.
Do I have any?
I
don't even have any diorite.
It just gets worse and worse.
It gets worse and worse.
This is crazy.
Give me 15 drills.
That's not even close to the amount I want right now.
Guess I gotta go find some iron.
And I don't need a lot.
I just need a little.
Shouldn't be too hard.
There's actually diorite right there, but...
I don't really want that.
Do I have any?
I may have cleaned this entire place of iron.
Although, I was digging a tunnel here.
And there were a couple spots where you could enter a different cave.
At least two spots.
Here.
Let's take it from here.
There we go.
I also don't have any torches because, of course, I don't.
Wait, what?
Oh, this is a different tunnel I dug.
Maybe here?
I like that there's light naturally here.
I don't have any torches.
Man.
That maneuver cost us literally 60 years.
Shit, there's nothing.
Let me think.
So, if I make a digging machine...
I guess I don't want it to be three high.
Two high is fine, right?
So, we can go 2x7 right now.
Which is not that bad.
But, if I'm gonna do this...
Like, I am thinking way bigger than that.
Oh, we also lost all our rails!
We need iron for that!
That's crazy, bro.
Oh, this is insane.
I had everything on me.
Wow.
Let's just find some iron, then.
I mean...
No reason to cry over something we can't change, right?
So, yeah.
Let's find some iron.
The good news is, I've already been in this cave, so...
There should be torches placed already here and there.
Man, Minecraft is a brutal-ass fucking game.
Like, it is straight-up brutal.
Dude, I wonder, is there a way to frickin' make iron?
I mean, yeah, that way.
I mean, it is...
It's...
It's an element.
Logically...
And then again, you know, you can turn some elements into other elements.
Wait.
It's fuckin' siltoch!
It's even worse!
It's not...
Oh, my God.
It's just...
It gets worse and worse.
It is absolutely insane.
I'm fumbling in the dark.
I feel like I'm slowly turning into some kind of creature in these caves, you know?
Whispers.
Of a shadow in the east.
Unnatural long life.
But you know what?
I think I may have enough iron.
And who knows?
Maybe I do have some rails lying around somewhere.
Because I was picking up a lot at one point.
You know, I was exploring a mine, and I just took rails left and right.
Now I gotta find my way out.
Just go up.
Hey!
I don't remember where I came from.
Oh, shit.
Okay, so we have lights there.
Is this...
Yeah, this is where I came from.
Good.
Grab this.
I guess I'm just gonna blast that.
Except I can't, because I don't have the blast configuration set up at home.
But I do have a blast oven that is stoked.
I'm just gonna use that.
That'll do for now.
How many do I have?
17?
Okay.
I mean, 17 is 17 drills.
Right?
But I think my bottleneck now isn't actually iron when it comes to that.
It's most likely the alloys.
Also, do I have extra lying around here?
Oh, yeah!
Very nice.
That's good.
The question is, how many do I need to make rails?
That's the big one.
I swear to God, this train will never be made.
I do all of this, by the way, in service of trying to figure out how to make a train.
Because in my mind, I'm like, okay.
Let's go to the end.
Let's go to the nether.
Let's find new blocks.
That'll potentially show me train parts, you know?
This train will never happen.
Never.
Oh, wait.
Blast this.
There we go.
That's good.
We can also turn these sink nuggets into...
No, can we?
Alloys?
Do I have more?
Show me the alloys.
I don't.
I wonder if I can turn andesite casings back into alloys.
Because look how many I have.
Three stacks.
There's also one here.
Let's see, though.
Alloy.
Andesite?
Don't I have a bunch of that?
No.
I don't.
That's why I needed the diorite, right?
To make andesite.
This is soon done.
And then for the drills.
How many can I make right now?
I can make eight?
Ooh, not bad.
Okay, so 23...
Is actually not bad.
We also need the other parts here.
So let's check for rails.
I wouldn't put them in here, would I?
Why would I put them?
Probably redstone.
Yeah, we don't have any rails!
Oh, that's painful.
What does it take to make...
Tell me it's easy.
Rails...
Just rail, I guess.
Oh, that's rough.
That's really rough.
Damn, son.
Man.
Okay, so wait.
Rails I need, so we need iron for that.
I also need to make the little thing you put on the rails.
Forgot the name of it.
Assembly cart?
Assemble something?
Cart assembler?
Two andesite alloy.
Oh, I just spent them all.
Unless I have more.
Do we have any...
Just two alloys.
I gotta have them.
Alloys.
Nothing.
I can't believe how much...
back I've been set by that incident.
It's actually...
Oh, we actually have some rails here.
Okay, that's good.
Nice.
That means less iron.
And you know what?
We can deal with 40 rails.
I can make that work.
40 is good.
I'm happy with that.
Now for the alloy.
Oh, beautiful.
We just have enough for two.
Ass.
Assembly.
Redstone dust and oak.
Give me one of these.
Nice.
Okay.
Next up, we need glue, which we have here.
And then, other than that, we need, I guess, a couple chests.
You know what we could do?
We could just assemble the whole thing here and then pick it up and take it with us later.
Right?
That's the ideal way to do it.
Let's make it here.
Oh, a switch.
What did I need?
I need something for...
Oh, redstone.
Redstone is what I need.
And a switch is pretty easy.
It's called a lever.
Oh, that's nice.
Okay, good.
Just make a couple more, I guess.
Let's also clean up.
Wait, how do I...
Oh, right.
It's weird, like, if I get keybinds with my foot.
You know, it's very different how your brain is wired.
Wait a minute.
What else did I need?
We have the lever now.
Oh, cobblestone.
Being specific, eh?
Don't just want normal stone.
Okay.
So we have...
Oh!
Dude, it is thundering outside in real life.
I love it.
Just like in the game.
Hold on.
I need to open the window.
Nice.
I love that, man.
That's the best feeling.
Okay, I'm happy now.
This is good.
This is exactly what I needed.
I'm going to litter over there.
Okay.
So, uh...
How am I going to do this?
So, 23 drills.
I guess we're going to do a 2 by...
11.
I guess we're going to do a...
It's still...
That's pretty good, right?
I mean, that's not bad.
So, we're going to do this.
That.
Oh, we also need deployers.
But I'm pretty sure I have a lot of those.
You know what?
Let's experiment with this.
I don't know how that's going to work, or if it even does, but we're going to try.
Anything else I could maybe use to make this even better?
Oh, I don't know.
There probably is.
So, I needed the deployers.
I'm pretty sure I had those at the factory.
Because, remember, I needed 9 deployers at some point, so I have leftovers, for sure.
Huh?
No, I gotta have some.
Where did they all go?
I don't believe that.
I mean, I guess I could take some from here.
Ow, ow, holy shit.
What is that even making over there?
I'm going to cannibalize this.
Give it to me.
Two.
That's all I need.
Yeah.
Go back.
So, now we have deployers.
Wait, where's my home?
I get so distracted when, you know, when you do that.
Hey, Jackie.
Jackie wants to something.
Play, maybe?
Oh, God.
Let's see if I remember how I set this up.
Pain.
Alright, it's facing the wrong way.
There we go.
Now, this one, I'm pretty sure, is correctly placed for the rails.
And then the next one needs to be one lower.
As weird as it sounds.
Like that.
Nice.
So, this one is for rails, and this one is for path.
And then...
I had a bunch of drills.
And the way I connected those...
I guess I put it straight on this.
So, we're just going to do this.
Can I use this to turn it, maybe?
No.
There we go.
Yeah.
We don't technically need to dig higher.
Although it is nice, I guess.
I mean, we can do one layer more.
Like, maybe three by seven or something.
Yeah.
I mean, that's looking good.
In my opinion.
That is a lot of digging, by the way.
Compared to what we had before, it's like...
It's more than twice.
You know?
Not bad.
And...
We should also...
I guess it will just connect like this.
Like, do we even need anything else?
So, obviously, we're going to...
Hey, Jackie.
Come here.
Come here, you.
There we go.
You want to lie right here?
Obviously, we're also going to...
Put some glue on this.
So, we glue all that.
We need the chests on top.
And then we need...
What else do we need?
Wait, I'm trying to think.
I'm holding Jackie in my arms right now, like a baby.
What's going on?
Daddy lost all his stuff in the nether today.
I know.
Oh my god.
She jumped off!
She's like...
Damn, I can't believe you did that, human.
I don't want to be associated with you.
Wow.
Betrayal.
Alright.
In the hour of support, where I need it the most, she left me.
That's crazy.
Alright.
Put this in there.
Golden chest plate, huh?
Don't eat that right now.
We should also prepare some proper food, by the way.
Just another thing on the list of many things that need to be done.
Oh, glue.
And chests.
Chests, chests, chests.
Where are thou?
Oh, I even have two.
Wonderful.
Is this good?
Let me think.
Yeah.
We don't need these up here.
Technically.
And you know what?
While we're at it, why don't we make it look nice?
You know?
Because right now, we need some good stuff.
We need some good vibes.
And this will give me good vibes, I think.
If we make it look nice.
So let's use a block that is nice looking.
For this.
What would that be?
I mean, glass is pretty cool, I guess.
Yeah.
Let's, uh...
Let's do that.
I like that.
Glassy mechanism.
No!
Broke the wrong thing.
Just feet things, you know?
That's what that was.
Okay.
Time for the glass.
Not bad.
That looks pretty sick.
I mean, it's not great, but it's okay.
Now, we also need a...
I'll say roller coaster.
A little wagon.
We can sit inside.
And I don't know where I have that.
Oh, it's gonna cost iron.
But we have iron.
Cart.
Wait, where do I have iron?
How am I able to make this?
Wait, I just happen to have five iron?
Huh?
How?
Uh, wait.
Did I have to include the...
Wait, no, no, no.
Here.
There.
And then here, we're gonna go like...
And then from here, we spread it out everywhere.
There we go.
Oh, and the chests.
Let's put the chests, uh, right here.
It's kinda nice.
Wait, no, actually.
Let's put them...
Like that.
I mean, why not?
Okay, it's not that beautiful, okay?
I get that the machine is ugly here.
I mean, look at this.
This is just disgusting.
I mean, it is an ugly machine.
I'm not gonna deny it.
It is.
But, uh, you know, it's functional.
And right now, it's all about revenge on the blocks.
We're gonna commit block genocide in the nether.
And I can't wait.
Uh, let's see.
Like that.
That has been connected.
And I think we are actually there!
Now, if I move this in there...
How come that's not, um, clicking into place?
Is that because of this?
Okay, good.
It's working!
That right there is working.
And I think we're done with that.
Like, we did it.
These go here.
And in the front, we're gonna have netherrack.
Netherrack.
A full stack for you.
There we go.
So the way this works now...
This is gonna place a block, uh, right here.
This is gonna place a rail in front of it.
And...
Hmm.
Oh, let me experiment with the...
Oh, but I lost that one now.
Oh, we had the little control panel thing...
That I didn't quite understand.
Controls.
Oh, that's gonna be expensive to make.
Electron tube.
I think I actually have that.
Yeah, I have three!
Okay, no problem.
And a button!
I think we can make that.
A button...
And then I think we had casing, yeah.
I wanna try and understand this.
So it seemed to me, like, in the ponder, that it just...
Turned it off and on, you know?
So, like, in that example, something was rotating.
And it just stopped it from rotating.
At that point.
Oh, wait, uh, pick it up.
Much easier.
Like that.
All actors off.
Oh, wait.
Is that turning off the drills, then?
That could be the case.
Why not, uh...
Go!
Huh?
Oh, wait a sec.
Um, I didn't actually glue that, did I?
Maybe that's why.
Oops.
Oh, no.
Oh, wait, what have I done?
No, it's still there.
Okay, weird.
Oh, oh.
Ah, look!
And now, when I turn it on.
Very confusing.
Also, can we...
Can we just go straight this time?
Okay, good.
So, right now, this...
All actors off.
This should not be digging through that, then, right?
Man, I hate that I can't push it properly with this panel in front.
Oh!
Wait, how did it go through it?
Shouldn't it have stopped in front of it, at least?
Or did I just turn this into, like...
What kind of veil walker?
It just walks through walls now?
That makes no sense.
That should have stopped.
Huh?
Usually, when it reaches a wall, it stops.
But let's try turning it on, then, and see what happens.
Okay.
Now we put this back.
Change this.
All actors on now?
Push.
Yeah, and then it's digging.
Okay!
Oh, shit, stop.
No more digging.
But, hey.
We know it's working now.
Actually, let's just go a bit.
I want to see if it's fully working.
Let's do a field test.
Literally, in the field.
It should create a little path, as well, when we go.
Ah, it can't do that, because of this.
Whoops.
And go.
No, no, no.
The other way.
Oh, it's so annoying.
I need...
You know what I need?
I need something, so I can push it.
We need a little push block.
Wait, is that even gonna work?
I guess we'll find out.
Okay.
Whoops.
No, no, no!
Okay, good.
I can't push!
Fuck!
Okay, you know what?
Fuck this panel.
I hate it.
Terrible panel.
I don't need this panel.
This is fine.
I want to see you dig.
I want to see you make a bridge.
Okay, it is totally working.
Confirmed.
Go back now.
Go back.
I said...
Back.
Back!
That's gonna produce a big digging area.
Can't wait.
Dude, I'm gonna come back with frickin'...
50.
Near the rights.
That's the only success criteria.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, is that what happened before?
I went into this?
But then there was a wall?
I feel like that shouldn't happen.
How am I able to go in this when there's a wall?
That feels buggy as hell.
Like, that's dumb.
Just let me not be able to go into the thing.
Wait, what?
Why can't I...
Okay, there we go.
Turn it on and now push it and pick it up.
Okay!
We got it!
We gotta work in a machine.
So that part is ready.
I guess this is fine here.
This is a crime.
Let's see if the windmill has produced some bread for me.
Hell yeah!
It's not fast, but...
It's something.
Bread.
How do I actually make it?
Just three in a line, okay.
Seven bread.
Kind of terrible.
This mill up here is really not producing a lot.
It's a pathetic mill.
Yeah, not a big fan.
We need a bigger area of crops.
That's what we need.
Are we ready for the nether?
Is it time?
Oh, oh!
Let's try it with the portable engine!
Actually, yeah.
That was the thing I wanted to try.
There's gotta be some way to do this.
We gotta figure out how to make this thing go on its own.
That's the next goal here.
If we can do that, then we're golden.
Okay, let me look at this thing again.
We're gonna ponder some stuff now.
Okay.
So it does...
Yeah, okay.
Yes.
Fuel can be inserted.
But that is not how we're gonna use this.
Wow, there's not even a second page on this.
Okay.
What's this?
Speedometer.
Okay.
We don't need that either.
What can I possibly...
use to accelerate this on its own?
I mean...
Ideally, you would say make a train, right?
Except I can't.
Let me see what else I can ponder here.
Logic components.
Item...
No.
Kinetic appliances.
Components which expose special behavior when attached to a moving contraption.
That's what we need.
Yeah.
Mechanical drill.
Deployer.
Mechanical bearing?
Does that have a special use when attached?
When they're...
Oh.
Oh, right.
Okay.
It's like a chicken head.
Wait a goddamn minute.
I wonder.
Think...
Check this out.
You know how in astronomy or like radio astronomy specifically you can't really build a you know 500 meter large telescope on Earth it would just collapse, right?
But you can build smaller telescopes over long distances and then use some really clever math to cover or simulate a large telescope.
What if we were to make a couple drills on the outside have it rotate around so that it sort of sweeps out an area that we're digging?
You know what I mean?
The problem is is it just gonna like when it digs this part is it just gonna move forward and then get stuck in there before it rotates?
I feel like that's gonna happen.
You know what I mean?
Hmm.
Hold on.
Let me just keep pondering.
Actually, let me see what else this one says.
Once again, the bearing will attach to the block in front of it.
Ooh.
Oh, wait, wait.
Ah, wait, wait.
Yeah, okay.
That's not gonna work that way, I don't think.
Wait, previous scene?
Oh, okay.
Funnel.
This is the one where the contraption control thingy was used as an example.
It will harvest and reset any nature crops in the way, yeah.
Seats.
I mean, I can sit on it while we go.
Wait, can I not make a little seat and a little pedal and then allow me to pedal manually?
Imagine sitting on it and then, I guess that's kind of what I'm doing when I'm pushing it.
Yeah.
Brass funnels can extract up to a full stack.
Okay.
Let me see what else this one says about drills.
Okay, so there...
Yes, we know this.
How come they're attaching it to this?
Maybe it's just standard.
Inventories attached will pick up the...
Yes?
Anything else I should know?
Give me some more, like...
I don't know.
Insider knowledge here.
Whenever deploys are moved as part of an animated contraption.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We know this.
Yes.
Yep.
What about...
Oh, maybe this is...
Maybe something here.
Radial chassis.
What's this down here?
Wait, navigation items?
Huh?
Components which offer a destination to...
Oh, okay.
We don't know what that is yet.
Interesting.
Huh.
Why is this highlighted?
Oh, copper casing.
Uninteresting.
I feel like, if anything, it should be in here, you know?
Components which expose special behavior when attached to a moving contraption.
there's gotta be some way to automatically make this thing move.
Like, there's just no way we cannot not do that.
You know what I mean?
Like, I don't believe it.
Maybe the saw?
Maybe there's something in there?
No saws on me.
Yeah, they're gonna do that.
Yes.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Wait, previous scene.
Oh, wait a minute.
So, if I go in here...
Oh!
We were already...
Oh, I see how this works now.
So, when I click on this over here, contraption actors, and then click on one of these, it's actually showing me the one, well, related to the contraptions, of course.
So, there's actually other pages.
It's just that it's defaulting to, you know, that one.
So, wait a minute.
Okay, let's think about this logically.
Movement requires either me pushing it or going downhill.
Downhill is one way to do it, but that's very inefficient and that's not gonna work in practice.
Oh!
Powered rails, I guess.
Oh, is that...
Wait, maybe that's just the answer.
Maybe powered rails are just automatically powered without redstone when it's part of this contraption?
I mean, all the other things are weirdly powered, right?
So, why not?
Is that the solution here?
I should have some...
Wait, powered rails.
Oh, I actually have all this.
Gold, stick, and redstone dust.
Nice.
Let's make like...
Well, six.
Oh, if this works, man...
It will be so elegant.
Now, this is gonna be turned on, so I don't wanna think that it's working just because this is powering it or something.
Is that on?
I can't...
Wait, is that on?
I can't tell.
I forgot how it looks like when it's on.
No, that's not on.
Shit!
Okay, check this out.
What if I attach a little redstone thing into the machine itself?
Maybe something there.
There's no way that works, right?
Something in motion that has redstone power?
Hmm, that seems questionable.
Oh, I guess we would have to do that.
I mean...
Ooh, wait!
No way.
Does that work?
Oh, it turns...
Oh, man!
That's too bad.
Damn!
Imagine, though.
Imagine.
I mean, okay.
One thing I could do...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
How long does the signal last, though?
Let's say I put redstone signal here, or power.
And it's all powered rails.
At that point, it's got a...
Is there actually a limit?
Hold on a minute.
I actually don't know this.
Powered rails.
Actually, just give me a bunch.
25.
We're gonna try something cool here.
Bring it back.
No, actually, we're gonna take that with us.
In a bit more space.
Ah!
Too bad.
Okay.
I thought maybe infinite.
I guess I could pick it up and put it down every time.
But is that really something you wanna do?
I mean, okay, it is definitely...
Instead of me using my back, you know, and exerting physical strength to continuously push this thing, I am flipping a switch continuously.
It's not bad.
It's still manual labor, though.
That's the problem, right?
And ideally, we wanna end up where it just goes on its own.
So...
I mean, I guess we have a better solution already.
Like, I think we already found something good here.
But let's see if we can find better.
We can definitely make it better.
I think the powered rails could be the solution, but what else do we have at our disposal?
Let me just have a look around at all the things we have.
Let me just ponder some random shit.
Something that could be related to railways or drilling machines or something, you know?
What do I wanna make?
Oh, wait, wait.
Controller rail.
What is this?
A unidirectional powered rail with variable speed controlled by the signal strength supplied to it.
Hold on.
Are there special rails?
I mean, other than that one?
For...
Hmm.
Wait a sec.
Controller rail.
Controlled by the signal strength supplied to it.
this is a create rail.
I feel like that could be important.
Oh, but it takes an electron tube.
It's a little expensive.
Those are not easy to come by.
What else can we use?
Sequenced gear shift.
Wait, I wonder.
If I do a mine cart with chest, is that just a more compact way of having it?
Because the mine cart I use right now is empty anyway.
So maybe I just have an extra chest.
You know?
Efficient use of space.
Oops.
Wrong tab.
Okay, hold on.
This may be it.
Something.
Okay, wait.
Steam engine.
What if I were to attach this?
I mean, it could just be something super dumb.
Like attaching the steam engine itself.
Let's actually ponder.
And who knows?
If you attach this to a contraption that's moving, maybe it just makes it go magically.
Who knows?
Things tend to just magically work when you attach them to contraptions, but it doesn't look like it.
Honestly, I don't think that was the answer.
It's gotta be this one.
Like...
Let's do the naive thing.
Let's not think about it too much.
What am I even doing here?
Just put the damn thing on.
Maybe that'll just work.
Also, we don't need...
We do need that right now.
Fucking a...
There we go.
Boom.
Now we need some fuel.
I've got some coal.
Coal, coal, coal.
Give me that.
Oh, I also have these.
Nice.
We can put them in here.
Wait, how does this work?
Oh!
Is it just gonna go?
Let's see.
Maybe it needs to push.
Oh, shit.
Why is it not going?
Are we missing a rail or...
Go!
Ah!
Push!
Why won't it...
Wait, what?
Why is it stuck?
Oh, wait, wait.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
We need glue.
Duh.
And let's remove this one, too.
Okay.
Did it run out of fuel?
Oh, I don't think it works.
Oh, man.
I was actually, like, 80% sure this was gonna be it.
Oh, no.
Do not fall in the hole.
I'm telling you.
Uh, okay.
Do that now, and then...
There we go.
Ah!
I mean, we have a working idea here, you know?
We can do detector or, uh, activator rails and just plop down the little flop, flop, flop.
Whenever we want to.
It's not...
It's better.
You know, it's not bad.
It works!
Or...
I guess it does.
I wonder how, um...
How much speed it's gonna get from that, you know?
Maybe it is so efficient that it's actually...
We don't need to look further than this.
This is it, you know?
Sticker?
I think we just haven't unlocked whatever we need for this.
There has to be a way to do it.
I refuse to believe there is not.
You know?
Yeah.
Wait, wait, what's that?
I'm still in contact?
Wait a minute, what is that?
Cobblestone?
Do I have one of these?
Contact.
I don't think I have it.
What did I need for it?
Contact.
One of the best movies ever.
Iron sheet.
Cobblestone.
I make two at a time?
Why is that?
Let's see here.
Redstone contacts facing each other will emit a redstone signal.
Ah, that's cool.
That's cool.
Okay.
That's neat.
Very cute.
So it's just like my windmill setup.
But with a redstone signal instead of dropping some wheat into a chute.
You know?
Very nice.
Alright.
I'll probably use that at some point for something.
Let's see what else we got.
I feel like maybe something with this, but the way this is written it doesn't sound like it's something we need.
You know?
Smart chute.
I don't think there's...
Okay, you know what I think we need here?
I think we need to make wheels.
Like, not out of rubber but out of iron.
You know?
Like, train wheels.
That's what we need.
Somehow.
Wait, maybe, uh, hold on.
Let me see this one again.
Physics assembler assembles blocks.
This is the really interesting one.
I actually almost haven't even played with this, but it's so fascinating the way that works.
And I'm definitely going to do things with that at some point.
This is what I was trying to think of, by the way, when I mentioned, uh, you know, taking a whole, I don't even know, like, big area of land and just letting it fall into lava, you know, and have the netherite survive the fall.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
This could be it.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
How did you do that?
Ooh, wait, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, we don't need rails.
Wait, do we?
We're just going to make a digging machine on, on, on those, on, like, the tank wheels.
Hold on.
Pause.
Look.
We make this, we make this exact freaking thing.
And we put the thingies on, in front.
Hey!
Let's do it, man!
We got everything we need.
We got this, we got, yeah, I'm just going to copy this exact design.
Exact design.
We're even going to put a little birdie on a little pillow.
Hell yeah.
Oh my god.
Wait, what if we're going to be able to turn it?
Can we turn, like, a wheel?
I'm going to make, wait, I have a better idea.
Fuck, fuck minecarts, dude.
I have a whole new idea now.
Back, back, back, back, back.
Show me, show me.
Show me just, this.
What even is this block?
Oh, polished blackstones?
This is polished blackstone stairs, I guess?
Don't know what that is.
Vertical gearbox.
Oh, right, so you're just turning all these, makes sense.
Clutch!
Ooh.
Hmm.
Okay.
How would I turn the, the other one though?
Like this one?
I guess you would turn this that way and the other one the other way.
So I guess you would need to have some kind of mechanism where you flip a switch and they would run opposite?
And I guess you do that with, what is it called?
The, um, basically I'm imagining a machine that can dig that I just drive myself.
You know what I mean?
Instead of just having to be reliant on a linear track, I can just go anywhere and I can dig the whole thing.
Oh my God!
We're gonna make it!
It's gonna be great.
Uh, I need, I need to figure out how to, uh, so to turn this we need to turn them opposite, right?
So there's gotta be something that does that.
Let's, let's see if we can find it.
Uh, chain drive, let's see here.
Wait, what was that?
Rock port.
I need to see everything again.
That could be important.
Maybe, I'll probably need a clutch.
I forgot exactly what that does, but it sounds like a thing I need, you know?
clockwork bearing.
I just, dude, I just got so excited because we're gonna abandon the minecart, which is so bad.
Like, it's amazing, but it's bad, you know?
Compared to this freedom that I'm imagining.
Uh, I guess tires?
No, we don't need those, actually.
We don't need tires where we're going.
Um, ear shift.
This, maybe.
We should try to make that.
Perhaps this just automatically freaking turns them the other way, you know?
Maybe that's like a thing.
Who knows?
Cockwheel, shaft, okay.
Maybe it's, you know, maybe it's been made easy like that.
Who knows?
And then we needed shaft.
I have it, nice.
What was that called?
What is this gonna say?
Steering wheels provide precise rotational output.
Hold right click to grab the wheel, okay, and move the mouse to rotate.
Oh, so it just rotates the shafts.
That makes so much sense, actually.
Sneaking while turning the wheel will, okay.
Oh, right.
So, like, on an airplane, you can have the fin in the back.
Smart.
So, basically, what I need to make is something that when I turn this left, it, or I guess we don't need to have a wheel for this.
We could just have a switch in a way.
One switch makes one of the, you know, the, in Danish we say laufel, which means larvae feet.
Turn the other way.
Right, or spin the other way.
Word for it in English, probably.
Okay.
I don't think I need to know about that.
That's cool.
Sure.
Okay.
Steering wheel.
I mean, that, that's a promising thing.
We can try that.
And then we can try other things.
Open this one.
We don't need propeller.
Surely.
probably a gearbox.
I forgot what it's called, the one that makes it turn the other way.
Maybe that is the clutch, actually.
Elevator pulley.
Okay, this is where I was.
Flywheel?
embellish your machines with this imposing wheel of brass.
When powered by kinetics, start spinning.
Okay.
Doesn't seem terribly useful.
This would be good if we made a car with wheels, but we don't make that.
Dude, there's like nothing I need here.
Metal girder.
Directional gearshift.
Wait, don't I have that?
I feel like I have that.
Gear shift.
I must have made that.
Clutch!
Let's take that.
Redstone contact.
Sequence the gear shift.
What was that again?
Relay rotation by following a timed list of instructions.
Don't think this is it.
No, that doesn't make sense to use.
Don't think I've made the whatever this one was just now.
Directional gearshift.
Let's make it.
Hell yeah!
Let's see.
Unpowered directional gearshifts do not relay rotational power.
when the straight side is powered it will relay rotation.
Oh yeah?
When the reverse side is powered it will reverse rotation.
Isn't that it?
When both sides are powered it will stop relaying rotation.
Oh.
I feel like this could be it.
How do I make this slow again?
Comfy reading.
When the straight side is powered wait straight what do you mean straight side?
Oh!
Straight as in okay I see.
It will relay the rotation.
Okay so imagine we have the engine it's spinning right?
The portable engine it's going in this direction.
So it's doing that now.
And that is currently spinning both of the sides of the tank I guess we're going to call it.
And then we have a little in-betweener for one of the sides.
Ah but we would have to then we can only turn one way.
Oh god this is blowing my mind already here.
Ah!
Let's just make the thing in the thing.
See what happens.
You know what I mean?
Let's just make it.
The exact same way and then we can take it from there.
Have a starting position here.
What can I get rid of?
I don't want this.
Clean the inventory.
Let's just see how it works before we do anything.
You know?
In you go.
All these little random things can go away.
Like glass for example.
I'm going to keep the clutch.
What was the clutch again?
It just stops rotation, right?
When you power.
Yeah.
Okay.
And powered rails.
Let's put them in here.
Redstone.
There we go.
Clean inventory.
Mostly.
Okay.
So the thing in the preview was for the steering wheel, I believe.
No, it was not.
It was for...
Let me actually see this one.
Remind me what it does.
Mount attached structures to passing mine carts.
Right.
Without a redstone signal, it disassembles.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
With the help of super glue, sure.
Using a wrench on the mine cart, will it carry it?
Oh, that's actually kind of cute, the way it turns.
cart contraptions will rotate to face towards their cart's motion.
Maybe this will say something about making it go on its own.
The assembler is set to lock rotate.
Yeah, sure.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, what's happening?
Whenever two cart assemblers share an attached structure?
Yeah.
Powering either of them will create a carriage contraption.
Say what?
Oh,
that's cool.
Oh, that's neat.
That is really cool.
I didn't know you could do that.
Wow.
I mean, it's not useful right now, but...
Wait, how would that be nice?
I mean, it's cool, I guess.
I don't really see a use case for it right now, though.
Cart assemblers on regular tracks will not affect the passing cart's motion.
Really?
won't it turn it into non-physics whatever?
Wait, hold on.
When on powered or controller rail, the cards will be held in place until it's powered.
What?
Oh, that's a nice quality of life.
I didn't know that.
Oh, that is fantastic.
Other types of mine cards can be used as the anchor.
Right.
So, like, with the chest or with this one, I guess.
Furnace cards will keep themselves powered, pulling fuel from any powered hot.
Wait, what do you mean powered?
Powered how?
You mean like moving?
Powered what?
That's it?
Hold on, fuck the tank for a moment.
Fuck the tank.
Back to this.
I thought it meant like powered as in it's going to power the components.
My cart?
There's no way.
furnace.
Furnace.
I mean, I'm still gonna...
Okay, oh my...
But now I'm obsessed with the freaking tank idea.
I don't want to...
Okay, I guess I...
Hmm...
Ah...
Wait, um...
Minecart.
Huh?
Why can't I click on it?
Oh, that's weird.
I need...
I need one more.
I can make it.
Just one more.
Apparently there's two versions of a minecart.
Don't know why.
Haha!
Wait, it's just gonna drive itself?
I can't wait to see this.
Oh, also, while I'm doing this, let me test the, um, the powered rail thing that we just read about.
That was also super nice.
The powered rail...
Just one...
No, one.
Uno.
I need this guy.
And that one.
And, uh...
Oh!
That one!
We're gonna remove this shit!
Nobody cares about that.
How do I remove?
Oh, right.
Remove that one.
Okay!
Uh, then we are gonna say goodbye to this thing, I guess.
And it's just gonna, it's gonna pull from...
Wait, it's gonna mine, uh, coal as it goes!
Aha!
It could, it's gonna burn that.
There's no way this works.
Turn it off.
Wait, what the hell?
Come on, come on.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh!
I thought it was gonna dig my house!
How come it's not working?
how come I cannot fill this up?
Maybe it needs coal.
Bro, what is going on here?
Wait, it ran out of tracks, I guess.
Oh!
I see.
Back again, back again.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Here we go.
Are you stupid?
I stopped because of this now.
But look, it's, uh, it's going.
This is it.
We...
And there was a simple solution after all.
It was just a minecart with a furnace inside of it.
Wow!
Okay.
That's very...
I mean, okay, I guess it makes sense in some way.
You know?
A furnace, like, okay, it's like stoking the oven on a steam train or whatever, you know?
You put fuel in there and it goes.
I see, I see.
How that makes sense somehow, but also it's not very intuitive.
I didn't even realize there were that many pages to the, uh, card assembler.
Man.
Okay, that's good.
But, okay, so we, we, it solved.
We solved it.
But can we find better?
Even better now?
Because, yes, this is great, but imagine if I can control it myself and drive it like a freaking car.
You know?
And, and I'd be like, okay, I'm gonna dig left now.
Oh, shit, we hit some lava.
Back up.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
When I'm going backwards, you know, fucking, that would be sick.
That's even better.
That's gotta be a way to do that.
Right?
Or even, we can even have the little, uh, the, the gym message, you know, when we back up.
Gym.
And then when we stop backing up, we go forwards.
It's great.
Gym.
You see the vision?
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Hold on, hold on.
Okay, so let me actually just build the thing I saw.
That's what I was gonna do, but then I somehow stumbled on that.
Uh, da-da-da-da-da.
Where did I see that anyway?
Was it this one?
Bam, bam.
It was something about movement.
Uh, movement, movement.
Let's look in here again.
There.
Could have been that one, actually.
Nope.
Oh, God, what was it?
Was it this one?
No.
Ah!
You know the one where they showed the...
the three different variations on it?
So what was the point, what was the focus of those scenes?
Uh, the one with the tank...
was clearly the...
It was...
Was it the wheel?
No.
Oh!
I know what it is!
The physics thingy!
It's this one!
That one!
Yeah!
Okay!
Now we're back here.
Let's pay attention.
Haha, airplanes.
That's crazy.
Imagine having a digging machine so efficient that you fly it around and just fly through a mountain.
It digs so fast, it just digs a hole as you're going.
Oh!
That's crazy.
Okay.
Let's study this thing.
So they have a one, two, three, four, five by three.
I'm going to copy it exactly.
Five by three.
Right?
Then they have an engine.
They put it on top of the casing.
They attach a cock wheel.
A big wheel.
And I'm assuming a smaller wheel on the other side.
that then connects to this shaft to spin these.
This shaft right here, we don't need that.
We don't care about that shit.
But yeah.
Sounds good, man.
Let's make it.
Hey, hey!
Let's do it.
I need wood.
I'm making the exact same design.
I'm stealing it.
Sue me!
Boom.
Except I'm doing it with oak.
Come after me.
Sounds good.
We're gonna put the andesite casing right there.
And then we're gonna need some shafts.
How do we make those?
It's shafting time.
Oh!
Not that!
I don't have that.
Don't do this to me.
Don't do this.
Maybe I have some at my factory.
In fact, maybe I even have shafts there.
Dem-dem-dem.
Damn.
Oh, I even had three levers here.
Sweet.
I guess belts, we can...
We could use some of...
I have those at home.
Oh, there are my deployers!
Fuck!
I missed them.
I knew I had more!
Damn!
Let's put these back, then.
Rotate them, you know.
Wait, no, no, no.
The other way.
Oh!
Oh, good.
How do I make this, uh...
Not suck.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Actually, that's nice.
Oh, man.
What the...
Ah, there we go.
There we go.
Down.
No!
I swear, the game is against me.
Like, how are you going every way except the right way?
It's doing every configuration except the singular one I need.
Blows my frickin' mind.
Gross.
I'm mad as hell.
And I'm not gonna take it anymore.
There's no fuckin' way!
My computer crashed.
What?
I'm back.
Oh my god.
That is insane.
Un...
I died in the saw.
I got processed.
Processed meat.
Oh my god.
And now it's playing...
Catch with my items.
That's fantastic.
I guess we're doing rails now.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Oh no.
Gimme...
Gimme this.
Oh my god.
Uh, rotate.
Wait, does it gotta...
Stop!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
No, wait.
It's too fast.
Spam.
That's right.
I'm getting it first, bitch.
No, am I?
I'm not.
Gimme.
Okay.
What a disaster.
Actually, I don't want this on me.
It's disgusting.
Uh, I think I also lost some wood here.
Slaps.
What?
Don't you dare die again!
I'm losing my mind!
This place is a hazard!
We can't have Osha come by here, I'm telling you that.
This is why we need coverings and safety regulations and rules.
And steel-toed boots, you know, and all that.
Safety goggles.
And what's happening here?
Crimes are being committed.
In real time.
Oh, man.
What a disaster, huh?
Uh, also, something looks off about this.
It doesn't look right.
What is wrong?
Wait, let me go inside.
I feel like I already fucked it up somehow, which is impossible.
What did I do wrong?
Wait, show me.
Come on.
It was three by what?
How many?
One, two, three.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay.
Oh, wait, there's slabs.
That's what's looking off.
I was like, it looks a little too thick and thonky for me, you know?
Not big a fan of that.
It's gotta, you know, have a bit of clearance.
Between, uh, the floor.
And the machine.
Otherwise, how is it gonna go?
So, so to make slabs, isn't it just...
Start looking it up.
Slap.
I don't remember.
Oh, yeah, just three in a line, right.
That's it.
Now we got it.
Oh, no.
Okay, and then?
Then, uh, we put in the rods.
But rods we don't have.
That's why I went over here.
That's why I did this.
Let's go find some rods.
I may cannibalize my creations over here just to get the rods.
I'm not even kidding.
I need to do this right now.
Like, this is not needed right now.
Nobody cares.
Thank you.
We're gonna take this too.
These rods are very important to me and my mission.
Do we have alloys hanging out somewhere?
No?
Okay.
No alloys.
Eight shafts?
It may actually be exactly enough.
No, we need more.
Do I cannibalize?
Man, what a sad situation I'm in here, you know?
Cannibalizing my freaking factory just to get some shafts.
This is despicable.
I'm doing everything I can, except the one thing I need to do, which is something I don't want to do.
Wait, is there no other way?
Is there no other way?
I guess andesite...
Fine, I'll go find some andesite, dammit.
I really don't like finding andesite.
It makes me unhappy.
But then when I turn them into andesite alloys, then I become happy.
So it's almost like I'm banking happiness when I do it, you know?
It's not immediate gratification, it is very soon gratification.
I could also take some diorite.
Let's be real.
Ain't nobody got time for that.
I'm going straight to the source, baby.
Andesite.
Wanna fight?
I can't...
Fighting with feet is difficult.
Let me just do this, and then...
Do this, and then...
Oh my god, I'm actually pro.
I feel like I'm using my whole body here.
Like, physically, I'm fighting him with my whole body.
I miss my old axe.
It had efficiency 5!
What a tragedy.
Truly.
One of the greatest tragedies of our generation.
Like, nothing else in the world matters, you know?
Me losing that axe, that's what matters.
That's the real shit.
At least that's how it feels in my mind right now.
I'm happy with that.
We can make a lot of alloys out of that.
Fantastic.
And you know what?
Maybe I'll let my digging machine loose in the real world as well a little bit.
When I finally get it working.
And then just grab, like, you know...
Sorry, my head was scratchy.
Grab a million andesite.
And diorite.
And everything else that ends in ite.
Ite.
And then we're gonna shaft it up.
Give me that and give me this.
Alloy me!
Ooh, yeah.
Now we're gonna shaft.
Look at...
Oh my god!
That's naughty.
56 shafts.
Very nice.
And then...
Top it all off.
We're gonna finish off with some...
Uh...
Belts!
Actually, don't I have more?
I thought I had belts at home.
How much of a fool I was.
I think that's what they did.
And then they had one here.
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
One more!
Actually.
Like this.
Wait, we actually just need...
We already have enough!
Because the way these work...
This will blow your mind.
Bup!
Ha ha ha ha!
Right?
We're gonna drive this thing!
Oh, I can't wait!
Okay.
Now.
Engine.
Rotate.
Shaft.
Boom.
No.
Wheel.
We need big and small alike.
Gimme.
Big.
Small.
Boom.
And then a big one.
Right...
There.
I don't like this part!
No clipping here!
Not in this house.
And I guess the way they connect this is...
Hmm.
How...
How would they do that?
I guess they...
They could just...
No.
No, no, no.
And then one down there.
That's the naive solution.
It works, I guess.
I guess?
All right.
But don't we also need the physics assembler?
I feel like that's the whole...
Kitten caboodle.
Of this here operation.
Anything else we're missing?
Let me think.
I mean, obviously we gotta steer it at some point.
But right now we're just...
I just wanna make go, you know?
Bop!
Whoa, that's cool.
Okay.
And now?
Now we're gonna...
Wait, what am I missing?
Why is it not...
Oh, we need fuel.
Fuel for Huel.
This tank will now be called Huel.
With two L's.
Yeah!
It's not going.
Oh!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Wait!
Ha ha ha ha!
This one fell down.
Yeah!
We need to glue!
We gotta glue this, son of a gun.
Maybe like that, and then...
I don't know how much I need to glue this.
Maybe I need to do this like that, and then like that, and like that, and this, and like that, and then a little bit of that, and this.
Surely that's the way.
What's all this?
Get rid of it.
Are we ready?
Are we ready to rock this city?
Oh, we probably need to glue this bastard too.
No, no, no, no.
Stop.
How to do this in a way that makes sense?
I can't reach the bottom...
Hold on.
Mole man activated.
Let's estimate where it is.
So it's one, two.
One.
Wait, why I can't die?
Fine.
I'll check the undercarriage.
Oh, I'm wearing...
Ha!
I was trying to use berries on it.
The old berry technique...
Didn't quite work out.
Hello?
I can't get out.
Fuck!
Wait, I can't do this.
What the hell is...
This is a mess.
There we go.
You ready?
Oh my god.
Wait a minute.
What have I done?
Oh, wait.
I think this is touching the floor, which is probably bad.
Or, wait, what?
How?
I...
I need to see something.
Show me once more Oh!
How thou's did this?
What
is...
What is that back there?
There's something in the back.
What is that?
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Go back.
There's a...
Wait, there's a belt there?
Why is there a belt there?
I think the issue right now is that these wheels are sort of, uh...
working against what I'm trying to do here.
Let me...
Yeah, we can't do this.
We gotta find a way to rotate this shaft without touching the floor, I think.
Which is actually impossible.
Unless...
Unless we can...
Wait, let me see this thing again.
One...
One last time!
One more time.
What is back there?
There's a mechanical belt!
Well, how does that make sense?
Oh!
I see!
I understand!
Watch.
They are...
Uh...
Get rid of this.
Shaft here.
I need belt.
They are...
They are using a belt that goes up like this to rotate the shaft itself, which is genius.
Oh my god.
Ah...
Beautiful.
That has to be it.
Give me like four.
Just so we have some at home.
Yes!
But it's the opposite way.
No, it's not.
It's perfect.
Ah, but wait a minute!
This is gonna...
Wait, isn't that gonna work against?
Hold on.
This is not gonna work, is it?
It be going!
Oh, it stopped!
Oh no, I'm trapped.
Ah, shit.
Oh, no.
Why do I get to look at the butt?
This thing is even being moved on it.
This is actually so dope, dude.
Yeah!
Wait, how's it gonna handle going down?
Let's see.
It's kinda slow though, isn't it?
Is it gonna go uphill?
Hold on.
Oh, this tree sucks ass.
It's a ta...
Oh no.
This is why we need a digging machine up front.
Oh, it's not going up!
It's a shitty tank.
That's the whole point of these, you know?
Oh my god.
But maybe...
Oh.
You know what I feel like right now?
I feel like the guy who does the Lego videos.
You know, when he makes things progressively more complicated to do certain tasks.
This is me.
I just had this idea of putting like...
You know how they in stunt movies have these rods they put in cars?
Uh, like pneumatic or whatever, uh, pressurized that make the cars flip.
So it looks good on camera.
I was thinking of putting in a rod that I activate that makes it go up at front, you know?
So it can go up things.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That would be kind of fun.
Uh...
It's working!
And we can definitely...
We can definitely put a digging machine up front.
Like, I'm just thinking ahead now how I want to make this so I can rotate it, you know?
If I can make this spin the other way...
While this spins one way...
Bro, how the hell do they even do that in real life?
That's kind of a crazy thing.
I guess you would need some kind of differential...
Whatever it's called.
Uh...
Not differential axle.
That's used to...
Uh...
You know...
Make it so that the front wheels of a car, for example, don't rotate the exact same.
But they can rotate a little off from each other, you know?
Turn this off!
How do I do that?
I guess I just do this.
Dude, this is so freaking cool that you can make this.
And how fast is this burning fuel?
Like, can I somehow look?
Oh!
Rotation direction!
Ah!
Now we go backwards!
Oh, sweet!
Okay.
So at least we have reverse figured out.
Nice.
Now to turn it, I guess we can just override.
Uh...
I guess we would have one here and one on the other side.
So that we override the direction.
So that this one still turns.
There's a way to do it.
There's definitely a way to do it.
Why did that stop?
Oh!
Ran out of fuel, I guess.
No more fuel for Huel!
Huel needs to take a break, and so do I.
Let's stop it there.
That was okay.
Like, I thought things got a little bit shitty at one point, you know, because I lost literally everything.
But other than that, I would say things went okay in the end.
It was nice to discover some new things.
And, uh, we already have a functioning, self-driving railroad, uh, digging machine.
So that one is in the bag.
That's the sound of it going in the bag.
But now we're also making a digging tank.
We're gonna call it Dank.
No.
Never mind.
The name is Huel.
There's a lot of good names for these.
Yeah.
That was good.
I think of Hank now.
Yeah, exactly.
Hank the tank.
Fitting music, too, with Hank.
You know?
When is the Isaac?
I stopped Isaac for now.
Oh, yeah.
I gotta use the goggles more.
That's true.
I lost my goggles in the great, uh, disaster of, I guess, 26, it would be.
It will go down as one of the worst that I have ever had.
Have I had a bigger loss than that?
Like, the amount of stuff I lost was incomprehensible to me.
Maybe I had something close, but it's been a while that I forgot.
What's your simulation distance?
I think 24 or 32.
Funniest thing is that you made that maze.
I know it's ironic.
I know.
It's so dumb.
And you know what?
In the end, it was greed.
Because I decided to stay longer than I should have.
Like, at one point, I considered going home.
And I was like, no, I need a bit more, you know?
I just had to squeeze the lemon.
Like a damn idiot.
I can't believe it.
How are you gonna move your tank to the nether?
Oh, easy.
I pick it up with my wrench, dude.
It's a contraption.
I just pick it up and take it with me.
Put it in my pocket.
Put it in my tummy.
Do you ever rage bait us on purpose?
Of course.
I do it all the time.
Haven't you heard?
It's all I do, actually.
I actually...
That's why I stream so little, you know?
I spend all my other time trying to plan how to make you guys as mad as possible.
I'm like Walter in the lab, you know?
Concocting the perfect rage bait.
Nah, I don't really do that on purpose.
Maybe sometimes I'll do it.
There is one thing I do in Detroit Become Human, at least.
That is on purpose, and it's quite funny to see people just eating it up, you know?
Hook, line, and sinker.
It's not the gazelle, actually.
It's something else.
It's not the animals.
It's something that people get quite mad about in the comments.
It was sort of the same thing that happened with...
Zelda Ocarina of Time at one point, you know?
Yeah, I'm loving Detroit so far.
It is a fantastic TV show for me.
That's what I look at it as, you know?
Where I get to influence certain parts of it, but yeah.
Yeah, all in all, wonderful experience so far.
Don't worry, I'm not going to spoil anything.
What do you mean when you're saying that you're playing with your feet?
No, no, what I'm saying is that I was going to have a meet.
No, I just play with my feet.
I use my feet to control the mouse.
Obviously, my left hand is on the keyboard, right?
Why are you question-marking it?
So, like, I have my left hand on the keyboard.
My right foot is, like, so...
Like, I have to contort a little bit, but I have my feet, like, on the table.
So I sit a little weird, you know?
And it's controlling a trackball.
With my foot.
I'm not kidding.
I was using my foot that way, but only for a little bit.
And then I used my hand on the trackball.
But I'm not kidding.
In the very beginning, I was playing with my foot.
Like, literally 100% rotund.
I had my foot on my table, controlling the mouse on the trackpad.
Rotund.
100%.
No, not...
I've not been playing the whole time like that.
It was just the very, like, five minutes, and then...
Whenever I would mention the foot afterwards...
It was still the trackball, but it was just my hand, right?
I'm still not good at it.
That's why I had shitty gameplay.
No, I've not been playing like that the whole time.
Like, almost.
Like, the last, maybe...
I guess two hours, I played with the trackball, yeah.
Toe cam is not happening.
I guess it would just be a mouse cam.
Oliver, some kids are in your stream.
Okay.
There's probably also some adults and some elderly people.
You want to know what happened with the death that you called a bug?
I think I know what happened.
I described it already, didn't I?
Not the elderly.
Can you go to the doctor for selective dementia?
Probably.
Am I gonna?
Probably not.
Update on the ADHD.
My doctor said she would contact me, but she hasn't contacted me yet, so I don't know.
Maybe she forgot.
I'm just waiting.
Who knows?
Maybe she's busy.
She was gonna get back to me about it.
When will you crush Orphids?
I will crush Orphids at some point, but it's not gonna be a crushing.
It's gonna be either a shredding or burning or gnawing or gnashing.
It's gonna be, you know, some other brutal way to kill them.
No, she didn't contact me.
They'll never get back to you?
You gotta call them?
Yeah, I'll probably will.
It was the call.
It was not.
It was a random spam.
That's one thing I love about new phones, you know?
They know which ones are spammers, usually.
It's nice.
What will I have for dinner?
I will...
Actually, I'm gonna have steak and frites, because I talked about it so much today.
I'm gonna go and get that from the store.
Actually, I already have a Pommer's frites in the freezer.
I just need a steak.
And probably some greens.
Lately, the greens I've been eating a lot, I've been kind of obsessed with them, are...
It's like weird, long, small broccoli type deals.
They look like broccoli, but they're like very tiny and long.
Do you know what I mean?
Like, I put them on the pan with some oil and some salt.
Broccoli...
Is it broccolini?
There's no way that's the name.
Broccolini.
Yeah, that's it!
I love those, man!
They're so good!
It's like my poor man's asparagus.
I do love asparagus on the pan like that.
But for some reason, they're so expensive!
These ones are less expensive.
But still kind of expensive.
Yeah, they're very nice.
I love them.
It's in the kale family.
Oh, so it's not a...
I guess it is a broccoli.
It's called broccolini.
They're so good.
You should try it.
Just on the pan, you know?
Give them some color.
Oh, broccoli's also in the kale family.
Hmm.
Well, there you go.
You guys like Brussels sprouts?
I hated them as a kid.
But then as an adult?
I still hated them.
I'm not a big fan.
I guess I can like them if they're prepared correctly.
Like, if they have some good Mayotte reaction on the pan, you know?
Some salt, maybe.
And maybe some...
I don't know.
Some kind of sauce with it.
Then I can...
I mean, I'll eat it.
If you serve it to me, I'll eat it, you know?
I'll eat pretty much anything people serve me, but...
Making it myself?
I don't know about that.
Okay, you know what?
Regarding the cooking stream?
It's gonna happen soon.
Uh, I'm gonna do it.
We're gonna do it.
No more bullshitting.
Now it's happening.
Like, not right now, but...
Like, extremely soon.
We're gonna do it.
Because I really wanna do it.
And I keep saying I'm gonna do it.
And I never do it.
So just like my son, Ben, we're gonna come in there and we're gonna do it.
I can't stop thinking about that video.
Please schedule it.
Okay, I promise to schedule it when I figure out when.
I just have to set up, like, a proper camera.
I don't want it to be, like, a scuffed stream, you know?
I don't wanna be, like, technical issues all the time and all that.
So I'll have to set up something that actually works.
I'm not sure how to actually do it, you know?
In a way that isn't super scuffed.
On Christmas?
No, I'll probably go to my family on Christmas.
Oh, actually, I wanted to add the Jackie emote.
Do you know where it is?
And which one specifically it is?
I do wanna add it.
I was looking for it at one point.
It's in the channel related.
Okay.
Let me see.
Yeah, well, I think I saw it in there, like, a long time ago.
But I couldn't find it.
Like, when I search for Jackie emote, there's just nothing.
Yeah, like, I also tried just searching for Jackie.
I'm not doing anything special for Halloween.
I'm, in general, not doing anything special.
I'm a very non-special guy.
But for Halloween, I'm definitely, like, I'm definitely gonna play a Halloween game on the channel.
Or not a Halloween game, but, like, a scary game.
I would say it is a thing in Europe, some places.
It is a thing in Denmark, but it's not, like, as crazy as in the United States.
Maybe you'll have some kids come by and ask for candy.
But it's only really gonna happen in certain, you know, neighborhoods.
And it's definitely not gonna happen in apartments like this.
But if you own a house and you're, like, in a suburban area...
Yeah, probably.
It'll be a thing.
Some horror mod in Minecraft.
Bro, I think that would kill me.
Minecraft is already a horror game in itself.
Making that especially scary would...
Like, even...
I'm thinking back on some of the horror stuff.
From the special map that...
Uh...
The pot made, you know?
And even then, I was...
That was terrible.
Like, horrible.
Just...
Too scary, man.
Too much.
Yeah, the pot.
Could you check your Discord DMs in our email?
I don't really respond to Discord DMs.
Like, I write in the...
Read Me channel that...
I don't do that.
Like, don't DM me there.
There's a lot of emails in my inbox.
A lot of them are spam.
I'll get around to answering some of them at some point.
I'm really not good at that.
I know that.
There's just so much crap in there.
Do people still send you spoilers?
Oh, yeah.
Definitely.
Even for Detroit Become Human, I've gotten a lot.
But I...
I see them a mile away.
Like, I don't even open them.
You know?
You can just tell what kind of mail it is.
Yeah.
The reason I mentioned it specifically for...
Silksong, for example, is because I got way more than usual.
I mean, I get people are excited.
They want me to experience everything, you know?
I mean, a lot of them are not, like, malicious.
It's not that...
At least I don't think so.
That they want to just ruin it for me.
There were a couple of those for Silksong.
It's just mostly people be like, Hey, you forgot to do whatever, you know?
Or you should really do that or something.
And it's just like...
No!
I'm not gonna do whatever you tell me to there.
It's weird.
Let me just experience it my way.
Yeah, I'll miss some things.
That's okay.
It's not from a place of, you know, bad intention that people do at Woosh.
They love the game that I'm playing, right?
And obviously they want me to experience the game in the same way they did.
Or at least get the same experience out of it.
And it's hard for people to, I think, understand that even if I don't experience the exact same thing they did, then I'm then gonna hate it or something.
I'm not, you know?
Everyone's experience is a little different.
Especially in a game designed to make everyone's experience a little different.
But they do it because they love the game, right?
It is from a place of love.
I get that.
I enjoy your content for your view on avoiding spoilers.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, that's what I would like to see, right?
When I...
But that's just me, I guess.
Like, I usually watch streamers that...
Like, I watch blind playthroughs myself, right?
That's the whole point of it, is to see their experience of it.
Well, it makes sense.
Uh, video busters...
I don't think it's that rare.
There's plenty of channels doing this.
You just gotta look for them.
They definitely exist.
It's not that rare a thing, you know?
Jack emote in the related channel of need.
Okay, okay.
Yes, that's the one!
That's the one!
I'm gonna download that.
It is being added.
For next stream.
Thank you.
If you guys have other ideas for emotes, feel free to, uh...
Put that in the channel as well.
Okay.
I'm gonna go...
To the store!
Get some meat.
And I'm gonna make myself some steaks...
With...
Potatoes.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you around.
And...
Detroit!
Right after this.
For those that are following that.
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.